export default [
{
    id: 1,
    question: 'What is 60 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['62','61','60','63'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [-1, 0, 1, 2, 3]
},
{
    id: 2,
    question: 'What is 60 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['62','57','56','59'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]
},
{
    id: 3,
    question: 'What is 60 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['59','58','55','60'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]
},
{
    id: 4,
    question: 'What is 60 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['55','60','58','57'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [2, 3, 4, 5, 6]
},
{
    id: 5,
    question: 'What is 60 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['57','54','58','56'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [3, 4, 5, 6, 7]
},
{
    id: 6,
    question: 'What is 60 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['58','55','53','57'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [4, 5, 6, 7, 8]
},
{
    id: 7,
    question: 'What is 60 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['55','57','54','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [5, 6, 7, 8, 9]
},
{
    id: 8,
    question: 'What is 60 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['56','53','51','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [6, 7, 8, 9, 10]
},
{
    id: 9,
    question: 'What is 60 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['52','55','49','51'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [7, 8, 9, 10, 11]
},
{
    id: 10,
    question: 'What is 60 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['53','52','51','54'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [10, 11, 9, 8, 7]
},
{
    id: 11,
    question: 'What is 60 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['53','48','49','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [9, 10, 11, 12, 13]
},
{
    id: 12,
    question: 'What is 60 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','46','50'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [10, 11, 12, 13, 14]
},
{
    id: 13,
    question: 'What is 60 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['45','47','48','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [11, 12, 13, 14, 15]
},
{
    id: 14,
    question: 'What is 60 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['48','50','49','47'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [12, 13, 14, 15, 16]
},
{
    id: 15,
    question: 'What is 60 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['43','47','46','45'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [13, 14, 15, 16, 17]
},
{
    id: 16,
    question: 'What is 60 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['47','42','45','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [14, 15, 16, 17, 18]
},
{
    id: 17,
    question: 'What is 60 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['45','46','44','47'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [15, 16, 17, 18, 19]
},
{
    id: 18,
    question: 'What is 60 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['43','42','46','45'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [16, 17, 18, 19, 20]
},
{
    id: 19,
    question: 'What is 60 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['39','42','41','40'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [17, 18, 19, 20, 21]
},
{
    id: 20,
    question: 'What is 60 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['39','41','43','44'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [18, 19, 20, 21, 22]
},
{
    id: 21,
    question: 'What is 60 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['39','40','37','38'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [19, 20, 21, 22, 23]
},
{
    id: 22,
    question: 'What is 60 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['38','36','39','37'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [20, 21, 22, 23, 24]
},
{
    id: 23,
    question: 'What is 60 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['38','35','36','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [21, 22, 23, 24, 25]
},
{
    id: 24,
    question: 'What is 60 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','38','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [22, 23, 24, 25, 26]
},
{
    id: 25,
    question: 'What is 60 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['34','38','35','36'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [23, 24, 25, 26, 27]
},
{
    id: 26,
    question: 'What is 60 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['38','35','36','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [24, 25, 26, 27, 28]
},
{
    id: 27,
    question: 'What is 60 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['34','33','32','35'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [25, 26, 27, 28, 29]
},
{
    id: 28,
    question: 'What is 60 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['33','34','36','35'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [26, 27, 28, 29, 30]
},
{
    id: 29,
    question: 'What is 60 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','31','29'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [27, 28, 29, 30, 31]
},
{
    id: 30,
    question: 'What is 60 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['29','32','31','33'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [28, 29, 30, 31, 32]
},
{
    id: 31,
    question: 'What is 60 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['32','30','29','28'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [29, 30, 31, 32, 33]
},
{
    id: 32,
    question: 'What is 60 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['27','28','29','30'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [30, 31, 32, 33, 34]
},
{
    id: 33,
    question: 'What is 60 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['31','25','28','30'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [31, 32, 33, 34, 35]
},
{
    id: 34,
    question: 'What is 60 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['28','27','26','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [32, 33, 34, 35, 36]
},
{
    id: 35,
    question: 'What is 60 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['29','28','26','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [33, 34, 35, 36, 37]
},
{
    id: 36,
    question: 'What is 60 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['25','27','24','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [34, 35, 36, 37, 38]
},
{
    id: 37,
    question: 'What is 60 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['24','21','27','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [35, 36, 37, 38, 39]
},
{
    id: 38,
    question: 'What is 60 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['24','23','22','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [36, 37, 38, 39, 40]
},
{
    id: 39,
    question: 'What is 60 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['25','22','19','23'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [37, 38, 39, 40, 41]
},
{
    id: 40,
    question: 'What is 60 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','21','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [38, 39, 40, 41, 42]
},
{
    id: 41,
    question: 'What is 60 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['22','23','20','18'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [39, 40, 41, 42, 43]
},
{
    id: 42,
    question: 'What is 60 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['21','19','20','16'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [40, 41, 42, 43, 44]
},
{
    id: 43,
    question: 'What is 60 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['15','19','21','18'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [41, 42, 43, 44, 45]
},
{
    id: 44,
    question: 'What is 60 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['20','17','18','19'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [42, 43, 44, 45, 46]
},
{
    id: 45,
    question: 'What is 60 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['16','19','15','17'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [43, 44, 45, 46, 47]
},
{
    id: 46,
    question: 'What is 60 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['17','18','12','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [44, 45, 46, 47, 48]
},
{
    id: 47,
    question: 'What is 60 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['13','14','12','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [45, 46, 47, 48, 49]
},
{
    id: 48,
    question: 'What is 60 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['15','16','10','13'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [46, 47, 48, 49, 50]
},
{
    id: 49,
    question: 'What is 60 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['12','9','13','15'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [47, 48, 49, 50, 51]
},
{
    id: 50,
    question: 'What is 60 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','9','12'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [48, 49, 50, 51, 52]
},
{
    id: 51,
    question: 'What is 60 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['10','7','9','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [49, 50, 51, 52, 53]
},
{
    id: 52,
    question: 'What is 60 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['11','12','10','9'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [50, 51, 52, 53, 54]
},
{
    id: 53,
    question: 'What is 60 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['8','10','11','9'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [51, 52, 53, 54, 55]
},
{
    id: 54,
    question: 'What is 60 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['7','6','9','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [52, 53, 54, 55, 56]
},
{
    id: 55,
    question: 'What is 60 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['9','7','8','6'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [53, 54, 55, 56, 57]
},
{
    id: 56,
    question: 'What is 60 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['2','3','8','5'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [54, 55, 56, 57, 58]
},
{
    id: 57,
    question: 'What is 60 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['4','3','1','2'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [55, 56, 57, 58, 59]
},
{
    id: 58,
    question: 'What is 60 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [56, 57, 58, 59, 60]
},
{
    id: 59,
    question: 'What is 60 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','0','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [57, 58, 59, 60, 61]
},
{
    id: 60,
    question: 'What is 60 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [58, 59, 60, 61, 62]
},
{
    id: 61,
    question: 'What is 60 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','0','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [61, 60, 62, 63, 64]
},
{
    id: 62,
    question: 'What is 61 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['62','60','64','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [60, 61, 62, 63, 64]
},
{
    id: 63,
    question: 'What is 61 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['59','62','60','58'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [61, 62, 63, 64, 65]
},
{
    id: 64,
    question: 'What is 61 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['59','60','57','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [62, 63, 64, 65, 66]
},
{
    id: 65,
    question: 'What is 61 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['56','58','55','60'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [63, 64, 65, 66, 67]
},
{
    id: 66,
    question: 'What is 61 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['59','54','57','58'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [64, 65, 66, 67, 68]
},
{
    id: 67,
    question: 'What is 61 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['58','54','56','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [65, 66, 67, 68, 69]
},
{
    id: 68,
    question: 'What is 61 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['53','55','56','58'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [66, 67, 68, 69, 70]
},
{
    id: 69,
    question: 'What is 61 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['51','52','54','55'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [67, 68, 69, 70, 71]
},
{
    id: 70,
    question: 'What is 61 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['55','53','51','56'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [68, 69, 70, 71, 72]
},
{
    id: 71,
    question: 'What is 61 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['55','53','52','50'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [71, 72, 70, 69, 68]
},
{
    id: 72,
    question: 'What is 61 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['53','51','52','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [70, 71, 72, 73, 74]
},
{
    id: 73,
    question: 'What is 61 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['51','53','50','52'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [71, 72, 73, 74, 75]
},
{
    id: 74,
    question: 'What is 61 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['48','50','49','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [72, 73, 74, 75, 76]
},
{
    id: 75,
    question: 'What is 61 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['48','46','45','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [73, 74, 75, 76, 77]
},
{
    id: 76,
    question: 'What is 61 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['45','50','47','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [74, 75, 76, 77, 78]
},
{
    id: 77,
    question: 'What is 61 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['46','44','43','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [75, 76, 77, 78, 79]
},
{
    id: 78,
    question: 'What is 61 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['42','45','44','43'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [76, 77, 78, 79, 80]
},
{
    id: 79,
    question: 'What is 61 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['42','47','45','44'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [77, 78, 79, 80, 81]
},
{
    id: 80,
    question: 'What is 61 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['41','45','44','43'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [78, 79, 80, 81, 82]
},
{
    id: 81,
    question: 'What is 61 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['44','39','40','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [79, 80, 81, 82, 83]
},
{
    id: 82,
    question: 'What is 61 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['39','41','43','40'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [80, 81, 82, 83, 84]
},
{
    id: 83,
    question: 'What is 61 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['40','39','42','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [81, 82, 83, 84, 85]
},
{
    id: 84,
    question: 'What is 61 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['40','38','41','39'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [82, 83, 84, 85, 86]
},
{
    id: 85,
    question: 'What is 61 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['40','38','39','36'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [83, 84, 85, 86, 87]
},
{
    id: 86,
    question: 'What is 61 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','40','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [84, 85, 86, 87, 88]
},
{
    id: 87,
    question: 'What is 61 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['36','34','38','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [85, 86, 87, 88, 89]
},
{
    id: 88,
    question: 'What is 61 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['35','36','37','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [86, 87, 88, 89, 90]
},
{
    id: 89,
    question: 'What is 61 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['35','32','33','34'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [87, 88, 89, 90, 91]
},
{
    id: 90,
    question: 'What is 61 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','33','30'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [88, 89, 90, 91, 92]
},
{
    id: 91,
    question: 'What is 61 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['33','35','32','30'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [89, 90, 91, 92, 93]
},
{
    id: 92,
    question: 'What is 61 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['28','31','30','32'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [90, 91, 92, 93, 94]
},
{
    id: 93,
    question: 'What is 61 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['28','29','32','30'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [91, 92, 93, 94, 95]
},
{
    id: 94,
    question: 'What is 61 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['28','32','30','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [92, 93, 94, 95, 96]
},
{
    id: 95,
    question: 'What is 61 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['26','31','29','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [93, 94, 95, 96, 97]
},
{
    id: 96,
    question: 'What is 61 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['26','28','24','27'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [94, 95, 96, 97, 98]
},
{
    id: 97,
    question: 'What is 61 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['23','26','27','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [95, 96, 97, 98, 99]
},
{
    id: 98,
    question: 'What is 61 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['25','26','28','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [96, 97, 98, 99, 100]
},
{
    id: 99,
    question: 'What is 61 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['24','21','25','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [97, 98, 99, 100, 101]
},
{
    id: 100,
    question: 'What is 61 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['24','20','22','23'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [98, 99, 100, 101, 102]
},
{
    id: 101,
    question: 'What is 61 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['23','22','21','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [99, 100, 101, 102, 103]
},
{
    id: 102,
    question: 'What is 61 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['22','21','24','20'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [100, 101, 102, 103, 104]
},
{
    id: 103,
    question: 'What is 61 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['17','20','22','23'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [101, 102, 103, 104, 105]
},
{
    id: 104,
    question: 'What is 61 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['17','19','16','18'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [102, 103, 104, 105, 106]
},
{
    id: 105,
    question: 'What is 61 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['21','19','18','16'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [103, 104, 105, 106, 107]
},
{
    id: 106,
    question: 'What is 61 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['14','19','15','17'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [104, 105, 106, 107, 108]
},
{
    id: 107,
    question: 'What is 61 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['18','16','13','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [105, 106, 107, 108, 109]
},
{
    id: 108,
    question: 'What is 61 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['13','12','15','14'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [106, 107, 108, 109, 110]
},
{
    id: 109,
    question: 'What is 61 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['17','15','16','14'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [107, 108, 109, 110, 111]
},
{
    id: 110,
    question: 'What is 61 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['13','15','12','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [108, 109, 110, 111, 112]
},
{
    id: 111,
    question: 'What is 61 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['9','15','11','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [109, 110, 111, 112, 113]
},
{
    id: 112,
    question: 'What is 61 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['12','11','13','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [110, 111, 112, 113, 114]
},
{
    id: 113,
    question: 'What is 61 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['10','12','9','11'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [111, 112, 113, 114, 115]
},
{
    id: 114,
    question: 'What is 61 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['8','7','9','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [112, 113, 114, 115, 116]
},
{
    id: 115,
    question: 'What is 61 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['9','11','8','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [113, 114, 115, 116, 117]
},
{
    id: 116,
    question: 'What is 61 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['10','8','9','7'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [114, 115, 116, 117, 118]
},
{
    id: 117,
    question: 'What is 61 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['3','5','6','8'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [115, 116, 117, 118, 119]
},
{
    id: 118,
    question: 'What is 61 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['2','5','3','4'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [116, 117, 118, 119, 120]
},
{
    id: 119,
    question: 'What is 61 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['5','6','4','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [117, 118, 119, 120, 121]
},
{
    id: 120,
    question: 'What is 61 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','2','1'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [118, 119, 120, 121, 122]
},
{
    id: 121,
    question: 'What is 61 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['2','0','1','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [119, 120, 121, 122, 123]
},
{
    id: 122,
    question: 'What is 61 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','2','1'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [120, 121, 122, 123, 124]
},
{
    id: 123,
    question: 'What is 61 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [123, 122, 124, 125, 126]
},
{
    id: 124,
    question: 'What is 62 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['61','62','65','64'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [122, 123, 124, 125, 126]
},
{
    id: 125,
    question: 'What is 62 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['61','64','58','62'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [123, 124, 125, 126, 127]
},
{
    id: 126,
    question: 'What is 62 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['59','60','57','61'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [124, 125, 126, 127, 128]
},
{
    id: 127,
    question: 'What is 62 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['59','61','62','60'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [125, 126, 127, 128, 129]
},
{
    id: 128,
    question: 'What is 62 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['55','57','56','58'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [126, 127, 128, 129, 130]
},
{
    id: 129,
    question: 'What is 62 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['55','54','57','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [127, 128, 129, 130, 131]
},
{
    id: 130,
    question: 'What is 62 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['56','59','57','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [128, 129, 130, 131, 132]
},
{
    id: 131,
    question: 'What is 62 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['58','56','55','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [129, 130, 131, 132, 133]
},
{
    id: 132,
    question: 'What is 62 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['51','52','54','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [130, 131, 132, 133, 134]
},
{
    id: 133,
    question: 'What is 62 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['50','53','52','55'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [133, 134, 132, 131, 130]
},
{
    id: 134,
    question: 'What is 62 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['54','53','52','55'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [132, 133, 134, 135, 136]
},
{
    id: 135,
    question: 'What is 62 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['49','54','50','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [133, 134, 135, 136, 137]
},
{
    id: 136,
    question: 'What is 62 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['49','52','48','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [134, 135, 136, 137, 138]
},
{
    id: 137,
    question: 'What is 62 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['50','46','49','51'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [135, 136, 137, 138, 139]
},
{
    id: 138,
    question: 'What is 62 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['50','48','49','51'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [136, 137, 138, 139, 140]
},
{
    id: 139,
    question: 'What is 62 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['45','50','48','47'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [137, 138, 139, 140, 141]
},
{
    id: 140,
    question: 'What is 62 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['44','48','47','46'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [138, 139, 140, 141, 142]
},
{
    id: 141,
    question: 'What is 62 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['46','43','47','45'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [139, 140, 141, 142, 143]
},
{
    id: 142,
    question: 'What is 62 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['47','46','44','41'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [140, 141, 142, 143, 144]
},
{
    id: 143,
    question: 'What is 62 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['40','41','45','43'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [141, 142, 143, 144, 145]
},
{
    id: 144,
    question: 'What is 62 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['45','43','44','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [142, 143, 144, 145, 146]
},
{
    id: 145,
    question: 'What is 62 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['42','43','41','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [143, 144, 145, 146, 147]
},
{
    id: 146,
    question: 'What is 62 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['42','41','39','40'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [144, 145, 146, 147, 148]
},
{
    id: 147,
    question: 'What is 62 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['41','42','39','40'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [145, 146, 147, 148, 149]
},
{
    id: 148,
    question: 'What is 62 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','35','41'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [146, 147, 148, 149, 150]
},
{
    id: 149,
    question: 'What is 62 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['37','34','36','39'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [147, 148, 149, 150, 151]
},
{
    id: 150,
    question: 'What is 62 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['36','33','35','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [148, 149, 150, 151, 152]
},
{
    id: 151,
    question: 'What is 62 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['32','36','33','35'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [149, 150, 151, 152, 153]
},
{
    id: 152,
    question: 'What is 62 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','31','34'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [150, 151, 152, 153, 154]
},
{
    id: 153,
    question: 'What is 62 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['34','35','36','33'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [151, 152, 153, 154, 155]
},
{
    id: 154,
    question: 'What is 62 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['34','33','30','32'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [152, 153, 154, 155, 156]
},
{
    id: 155,
    question: 'What is 62 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['34','31','32','33'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [153, 154, 155, 156, 157]
},
{
    id: 156,
    question: 'What is 62 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['33','32','30','28'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [154, 155, 156, 157, 158]
},
{
    id: 157,
    question: 'What is 62 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['29','31','30','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [155, 156, 157, 158, 159]
},
{
    id: 158,
    question: 'What is 62 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['26','30','29','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [156, 157, 158, 159, 160]
},
{
    id: 159,
    question: 'What is 62 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['25','27','30','26'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [157, 158, 159, 160, 161]
},
{
    id: 160,
    question: 'What is 62 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['29','28','27','26'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [158, 159, 160, 161, 162]
},
{
    id: 161,
    question: 'What is 62 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['22','25','23','24'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [159, 160, 161, 162, 163]
},
{
    id: 162,
    question: 'What is 62 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['23','21','22','24'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [160, 161, 162, 163, 164]
},
{
    id: 163,
    question: 'What is 62 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['23','22','25','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [161, 162, 163, 164, 165]
},
{
    id: 164,
    question: 'What is 62 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['25','22','19','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [162, 163, 164, 165, 166]
},
{
    id: 165,
    question: 'What is 62 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['21','19','22','20'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [163, 164, 165, 166, 167]
},
{
    id: 166,
    question: 'What is 62 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['18','23','20','21'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [164, 165, 166, 167, 168]
},
{
    id: 167,
    question: 'What is 62 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['16','17','22','19'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [165, 166, 167, 168, 169]
},
{
    id: 168,
    question: 'What is 62 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['17','16','20','18'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [166, 167, 168, 169, 170]
},
{
    id: 169,
    question: 'What is 62 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['16','15','17','20'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [167, 168, 169, 170, 171]
},
{
    id: 170,
    question: 'What is 62 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','16','18'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [168, 169, 170, 171, 172]
},
{
    id: 171,
    question: 'What is 62 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['14','16','18','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [169, 170, 171, 172, 173]
},
{
    id: 172,
    question: 'What is 62 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['11','13','14','16'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [170, 171, 172, 173, 174]
},
{
    id: 173,
    question: 'What is 62 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','16','13'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [171, 172, 173, 174, 175]
},
{
    id: 174,
    question: 'What is 62 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','13','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [172, 173, 174, 175, 176]
},
{
    id: 175,
    question: 'What is 62 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','8','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [173, 174, 175, 176, 177]
},
{
    id: 176,
    question: 'What is 62 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','13','8'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [174, 175, 176, 177, 178]
},
{
    id: 177,
    question: 'What is 62 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['9','6','10','11'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [175, 176, 177, 178, 179]
},
{
    id: 178,
    question: 'What is 62 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['6','10','7','8'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [176, 177, 178, 179, 180]
},
{
    id: 179,
    question: 'What is 62 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['7','8','6','5'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [177, 178, 179, 180, 181]
},
{
    id: 180,
    question: 'What is 62 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['6','4','3','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [178, 179, 180, 181, 182]
},
{
    id: 181,
    question: 'What is 62 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['3','7','4','5'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [179, 180, 181, 182, 183]
},
{
    id: 182,
    question: 'What is 62 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['3','6','2','4'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [180, 181, 182, 183, 184]
},
{
    id: 183,
    question: 'What is 62 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [181, 182, 183, 184, 185]
},
{
    id: 184,
    question: 'What is 62 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','3','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [182, 183, 184, 185, 186]
},
{
    id: 185,
    question: 'What is 62 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [183, 184, 185, 186, 187]
},
{
    id: 186,
    question: 'What is 62 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [186, 185, 187, 188, 189]
},
{
    id: 187,
    question: 'What is 63 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['63','62','61','60'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [185, 186, 187, 188, 189]
},
{
    id: 188,
    question: 'What is 63 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['64','65','61','62'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [186, 187, 188, 189, 190]
},
{
    id: 189,
    question: 'What is 63 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['64','61','63','60'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [187, 188, 189, 190, 191]
},
{
    id: 190,
    question: 'What is 63 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['60','58','57','59'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [188, 189, 190, 191, 192]
},
{
    id: 191,
    question: 'What is 63 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['57','59','58','61'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [189, 190, 191, 192, 193]
},
{
    id: 192,
    question: 'What is 63 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['61','60','58','59'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [190, 191, 192, 193, 194]
},
{
    id: 193,
    question: 'What is 63 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['57','54','55','59'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [191, 192, 193, 194, 195]
},
{
    id: 194,
    question: 'What is 63 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['56','55','54','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [192, 193, 194, 195, 196]
},
{
    id: 195,
    question: 'What is 63 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['58','55','53','56'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [193, 194, 195, 196, 197]
},
{
    id: 196,
    question: 'What is 63 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['56','51','55','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [196, 197, 195, 194, 193]
},
{
    id: 197,
    question: 'What is 63 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['50','51','55','53'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [195, 196, 197, 198, 199]
},
{
    id: 198,
    question: 'What is 63 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['52','50','51','54'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [196, 197, 198, 199, 200]
},
{
    id: 199,
    question: 'What is 63 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['51','53','54','52'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [197, 198, 199, 200, 201]
},
{
    id: 200,
    question: 'What is 63 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['47','50','53','49'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [198, 199, 200, 201, 202]
},
{
    id: 201,
    question: 'What is 63 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['48','46','49','50'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [199, 200, 201, 202, 203]
},
{
    id: 202,
    question: 'What is 63 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['49','47','50','48'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [200, 201, 202, 203, 204]
},
{
    id: 203,
    question: 'What is 63 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['50','45','47','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [201, 202, 203, 204, 205]
},
{
    id: 204,
    question: 'What is 63 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['45','46','44','47'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [202, 203, 204, 205, 206]
},
{
    id: 205,
    question: 'What is 63 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['45','44','43','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [203, 204, 205, 206, 207]
},
{
    id: 206,
    question: 'What is 63 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['43','44','42','45'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [204, 205, 206, 207, 208]
},
{
    id: 207,
    question: 'What is 63 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['43','40','41','44'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [205, 206, 207, 208, 209]
},
{
    id: 208,
    question: 'What is 63 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['45','42','40','41'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [206, 207, 208, 209, 210]
},
{
    id: 209,
    question: 'What is 63 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['43','41','44','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [207, 208, 209, 210, 211]
},
{
    id: 210,
    question: 'What is 63 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['42','40','43','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [208, 209, 210, 211, 212]
},
{
    id: 211,
    question: 'What is 63 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['39','37','38','36'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [209, 210, 211, 212, 213]
},
{
    id: 212,
    question: 'What is 63 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['35','39','40','38'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [210, 211, 212, 213, 214]
},
{
    id: 213,
    question: 'What is 63 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','40','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [211, 212, 213, 214, 215]
},
{
    id: 214,
    question: 'What is 63 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','39','36'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [212, 213, 214, 215, 216]
},
{
    id: 215,
    question: 'What is 63 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['35','36','37','38'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [213, 214, 215, 216, 217]
},
{
    id: 216,
    question: 'What is 63 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['34','32','33','36'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [214, 215, 216, 217, 218]
},
{
    id: 217,
    question: 'What is 63 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['33','32','35','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [215, 216, 217, 218, 219]
},
{
    id: 218,
    question: 'What is 63 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['31','32','29','30'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [216, 217, 218, 219, 220]
},
{
    id: 219,
    question: 'What is 63 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['31','30','33','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [217, 218, 219, 220, 221]
},
{
    id: 220,
    question: 'What is 63 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['30','28','31','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [218, 219, 220, 221, 222]
},
{
    id: 221,
    question: 'What is 63 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['32','30','28','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [219, 220, 221, 222, 223]
},
{
    id: 222,
    question: 'What is 63 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['29','30','31','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [220, 221, 222, 223, 224]
},
{
    id: 223,
    question: 'What is 63 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['24','27','25','28'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [221, 222, 223, 224, 225]
},
{
    id: 224,
    question: 'What is 63 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['29','25','26','27'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [222, 223, 224, 225, 226]
},
{
    id: 225,
    question: 'What is 63 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['25','26','28','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [223, 224, 225, 226, 227]
},
{
    id: 226,
    question: 'What is 63 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','27','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [224, 225, 226, 227, 228]
},
{
    id: 227,
    question: 'What is 63 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['24','23','22','20'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [225, 226, 227, 228, 229]
},
{
    id: 228,
    question: 'What is 63 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','21','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [226, 227, 228, 229, 230]
},
{
    id: 229,
    question: 'What is 63 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['20','22','21','19'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [227, 228, 229, 230, 231]
},
{
    id: 230,
    question: 'What is 63 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['22','20','21','18'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [228, 229, 230, 231, 232]
},
{
    id: 231,
    question: 'What is 63 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['19','22','21','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [229, 230, 231, 232, 233]
},
{
    id: 232,
    question: 'What is 63 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['15','18','20','16'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [230, 231, 232, 233, 234]
},
{
    id: 233,
    question: 'What is 63 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['15','14','17','16'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [231, 232, 233, 234, 235]
},
{
    id: 234,
    question: 'What is 63 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['16','19','18','17'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [232, 233, 234, 235, 236]
},
{
    id: 235,
    question: 'What is 63 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['16','17','18','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [233, 234, 235, 236, 237]
},
{
    id: 236,
    question: 'What is 63 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['14','12','16','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [234, 235, 236, 237, 238]
},
{
    id: 237,
    question: 'What is 63 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['15','14','13','16'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [235, 236, 237, 238, 239]
},
{
    id: 238,
    question: 'What is 63 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['12','10','9','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [236, 237, 238, 239, 240]
},
{
    id: 239,
    question: 'What is 63 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['10','12','11','9'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [237, 238, 239, 240, 241]
},
{
    id: 240,
    question: 'What is 63 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['12','11','10','13'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [238, 239, 240, 241, 242]
},
{
    id: 241,
    question: 'What is 63 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['9','6','11','12'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [239, 240, 241, 242, 243]
},
{
    id: 242,
    question: 'What is 63 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['8','6','7','5'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [240, 241, 242, 243, 244]
},
{
    id: 243,
    question: 'What is 63 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['8','10','9','7'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [241, 242, 243, 244, 245]
},
{
    id: 244,
    question: 'What is 63 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['6','9','8','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [242, 243, 244, 245, 246]
},
{
    id: 245,
    question: 'What is 63 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['4','5','3','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [243, 244, 245, 246, 247]
},
{
    id: 246,
    question: 'What is 63 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['7','4','6','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [244, 245, 246, 247, 248]
},
{
    id: 247,
    question: 'What is 63 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [245, 246, 247, 248, 249]
},
{
    id: 248,
    question: 'What is 63 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [246, 247, 248, 249, 250]
},
{
    id: 249,
    question: 'What is 63 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','0','1'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [247, 248, 249, 250, 251]
},
{
    id: 250,
    question: 'What is 63 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['2','1','3','0'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [250, 249, 251, 252, 253]
},
{
    id: 251,
    question: 'What is 64 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['61','62','63','64'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [249, 250, 251, 252, 253]
},
{
    id: 252,
    question: 'What is 64 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['63','60','61','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [250, 251, 252, 253, 254]
},
{
    id: 253,
    question: 'What is 64 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['65','64','62','59'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [251, 252, 253, 254, 255]
},
{
    id: 254,
    question: 'What is 64 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['64','58','59','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [252, 253, 254, 255, 256]
},
{
    id: 255,
    question: 'What is 64 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['58','60','61','63'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [253, 254, 255, 256, 257]
},
{
    id: 256,
    question: 'What is 64 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['60','56','59','61'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [254, 255, 256, 257, 258]
},
{
    id: 257,
    question: 'What is 64 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['58','61','60','59'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [255, 256, 257, 258, 259]
},
{
    id: 258,
    question: 'What is 64 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['57','59','55','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [256, 257, 258, 259, 260]
},
{
    id: 259,
    question: 'What is 64 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['57','54','56','55'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [257, 258, 259, 260, 261]
},
{
    id: 260,
    question: 'What is 64 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['56','52','55','58'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [260, 261, 259, 258, 257]
},
{
    id: 261,
    question: 'What is 64 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['51','52','54','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [259, 260, 261, 262, 263]
},
{
    id: 262,
    question: 'What is 64 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['54','53','51','55'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [260, 261, 262, 263, 264]
},
{
    id: 263,
    question: 'What is 64 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['52','53','54','55'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [261, 262, 263, 264, 265]
},
{
    id: 264,
    question: 'What is 64 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['51','53','54','52'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [262, 263, 264, 265, 266]
},
{
    id: 265,
    question: 'What is 64 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['50','53','52','49'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [263, 264, 265, 266, 267]
},
{
    id: 266,
    question: 'What is 64 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['49','46','52','51'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [264, 265, 266, 267, 268]
},
{
    id: 267,
    question: 'What is 64 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['47','45','46','48'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [265, 266, 267, 268, 269]
},
{
    id: 268,
    question: 'What is 64 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['46','50','47','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [266, 267, 268, 269, 270]
},
{
    id: 269,
    question: 'What is 64 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','46','45'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [267, 268, 269, 270, 271]
},
{
    id: 270,
    question: 'What is 64 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['46','44','45','47'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [268, 269, 270, 271, 272]
},
{
    id: 271,
    question: 'What is 64 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['47','43','45','44'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [269, 270, 271, 272, 273]
},
{
    id: 272,
    question: 'What is 64 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['40','41','43','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [270, 271, 272, 273, 274]
},
{
    id: 273,
    question: 'What is 64 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['42','45','41','44'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [271, 272, 273, 274, 275]
},
{
    id: 274,
    question: 'What is 64 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['43','40','41','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [272, 273, 274, 275, 276]
},
{
    id: 275,
    question: 'What is 64 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['39','43','38','40'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [273, 274, 275, 276, 277]
},
{
    id: 276,
    question: 'What is 64 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['39','41','42','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [274, 275, 276, 277, 278]
},
{
    id: 277,
    question: 'What is 64 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['41','38','36','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [275, 276, 277, 278, 279]
},
{
    id: 278,
    question: 'What is 64 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['37','38','39','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [276, 277, 278, 279, 280]
},
{
    id: 279,
    question: 'What is 64 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['36','39','37','38'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [277, 278, 279, 280, 281]
},
{
    id: 280,
    question: 'What is 64 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['37','35','36','38'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [278, 279, 280, 281, 282]
},
{
    id: 281,
    question: 'What is 64 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['36','34','37','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [279, 280, 281, 282, 283]
},
{
    id: 282,
    question: 'What is 64 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['33','35','31','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [280, 281, 282, 283, 284]
},
{
    id: 283,
    question: 'What is 64 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['30','32','35','29'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [281, 282, 283, 284, 285]
},
{
    id: 284,
    question: 'What is 64 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['30','29','31','28'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [282, 283, 284, 285, 286]
},
{
    id: 285,
    question: 'What is 64 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['31','32','30','33'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [283, 284, 285, 286, 287]
},
{
    id: 286,
    question: 'What is 64 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['31','28','27','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [284, 285, 286, 287, 288]
},
{
    id: 287,
    question: 'What is 64 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['31','25','28','27'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [285, 286, 287, 288, 289]
},
{
    id: 288,
    question: 'What is 64 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['24','27','25','26'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [286, 287, 288, 289, 290]
},
{
    id: 289,
    question: 'What is 64 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['28','26','25','24'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [287, 288, 289, 290, 291]
},
{
    id: 290,
    question: 'What is 64 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['24','25','22','23'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [288, 289, 290, 291, 292]
},
{
    id: 291,
    question: 'What is 64 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['24','25','23','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [289, 290, 291, 292, 293]
},
{
    id: 292,
    question: 'What is 64 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['24','20','23','22'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [290, 291, 292, 293, 294]
},
{
    id: 293,
    question: 'What is 64 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['25','22','21','19'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [291, 292, 293, 294, 295]
},
{
    id: 294,
    question: 'What is 64 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['19','20','22','21'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [292, 293, 294, 295, 296]
},
{
    id: 295,
    question: 'What is 64 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['20','18','19','22'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [293, 294, 295, 296, 297]
},
{
    id: 296,
    question: 'What is 64 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['17','21','22','19'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [294, 295, 296, 297, 298]
},
{
    id: 297,
    question: 'What is 64 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['18','16','17','21'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [295, 296, 297, 298, 299]
},
{
    id: 298,
    question: 'What is 64 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['20','17','18','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [296, 297, 298, 299, 300]
},
{
    id: 299,
    question: 'What is 64 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['18','13','16','19'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [297, 298, 299, 300, 301]
},
{
    id: 300,
    question: 'What is 64 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['14','12','13','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [298, 299, 300, 301, 302]
},
{
    id: 301,
    question: 'What is 64 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['14','17','15','11'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [299, 300, 301, 302, 303]
},
{
    id: 302,
    question: 'What is 64 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['16','11','13','14'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [300, 301, 302, 303, 304]
},
{
    id: 303,
    question: 'What is 64 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['10','12','11','9'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [301, 302, 303, 304, 305]
},
{
    id: 304,
    question: 'What is 64 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['9','11','14','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [302, 303, 304, 305, 306]
},
{
    id: 305,
    question: 'What is 64 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['10','7','11','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [303, 304, 305, 306, 307]
},
{
    id: 306,
    question: 'What is 64 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['9','7','6','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [304, 305, 306, 307, 308]
},
{
    id: 307,
    question: 'What is 64 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['8','10','5','11'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [305, 306, 307, 308, 309]
},
{
    id: 308,
    question: 'What is 64 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['5','8','7','9'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [306, 307, 308, 309, 310]
},
{
    id: 309,
    question: 'What is 64 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['6','4','9','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [307, 308, 309, 310, 311]
},
{
    id: 310,
    question: 'What is 64 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['5','6','8','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [308, 309, 310, 311, 312]
},
{
    id: 311,
    question: 'What is 64 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['4','7','6','1'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [309, 310, 311, 312, 313]
},
{
    id: 312,
    question: 'What is 64 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [310, 311, 312, 313, 314]
},
{
    id: 313,
    question: 'What is 64 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [311, 312, 313, 314, 315]
},
{
    id: 314,
    question: 'What is 64 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [312, 313, 314, 315, 316]
},
{
    id: 315,
    question: 'What is 64 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['2','0','3','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [315, 314, 316, 317, 318]
},
{
    id: 316,
    question: 'What is 65 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['64','67','63','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [314, 315, 316, 317, 318]
},
{
    id: 317,
    question: 'What is 65 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['63','64','65','66'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [315, 316, 317, 318, 319]
},
{
    id: 318,
    question: 'What is 65 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['62','61','63','60'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [316, 317, 318, 319, 320]
},
{
    id: 319,
    question: 'What is 65 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['62','63','64','60'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [317, 318, 319, 320, 321]
},
{
    id: 320,
    question: 'What is 65 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['61','60','64','59'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [318, 319, 320, 321, 322]
},
{
    id: 321,
    question: 'What is 65 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['61','59','57','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [319, 320, 321, 322, 323]
},
{
    id: 322,
    question: 'What is 65 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['59','60','58','62'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [320, 321, 322, 323, 324]
},
{
    id: 323,
    question: 'What is 65 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['55','58','57','56'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [321, 322, 323, 324, 325]
},
{
    id: 324,
    question: 'What is 65 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['55','54','58','57'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [322, 323, 324, 325, 326]
},
{
    id: 325,
    question: 'What is 65 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['55','53','54','56'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [325, 326, 324, 323, 322]
},
{
    id: 326,
    question: 'What is 65 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['56','52','53','55'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [324, 325, 326, 327, 328]
},
{
    id: 327,
    question: 'What is 65 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['54','57','53','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [325, 326, 327, 328, 329]
},
{
    id: 328,
    question: 'What is 65 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['53','52','56','50'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [326, 327, 328, 329, 330]
},
{
    id: 329,
    question: 'What is 65 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['52','54','51','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [327, 328, 329, 330, 331]
},
{
    id: 330,
    question: 'What is 65 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['51','54','53','52'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [328, 329, 330, 331, 332]
},
{
    id: 331,
    question: 'What is 65 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['51','50','48','49'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [329, 330, 331, 332, 333]
},
{
    id: 332,
    question: 'What is 65 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['49','46','47','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [330, 331, 332, 333, 334]
},
{
    id: 333,
    question: 'What is 65 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['47','50','48','45'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [331, 332, 333, 334, 335]
},
{
    id: 334,
    question: 'What is 65 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','46','50'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [332, 333, 334, 335, 336]
},
{
    id: 335,
    question: 'What is 65 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['43','46','45','48'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [333, 334, 335, 336, 337]
},
{
    id: 336,
    question: 'What is 65 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['45','47','46','44'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [334, 335, 336, 337, 338]
},
{
    id: 337,
    question: 'What is 65 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['42','46','44','45'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [335, 336, 337, 338, 339]
},
{
    id: 338,
    question: 'What is 65 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['43','40','45','46'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [336, 337, 338, 339, 340]
},
{
    id: 339,
    question: 'What is 65 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['40','42','39','45'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [337, 338, 339, 340, 341]
},
{
    id: 340,
    question: 'What is 65 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['43','41','39','38'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [338, 339, 340, 341, 342]
},
{
    id: 341,
    question: 'What is 65 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['40','38','42','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [339, 340, 341, 342, 343]
},
{
    id: 342,
    question: 'What is 65 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['41','42','36','39'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [340, 341, 342, 343, 344]
},
{
    id: 343,
    question: 'What is 65 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['38','36','41','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [341, 342, 343, 344, 345]
},
{
    id: 344,
    question: 'What is 65 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['40','37','36','35'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [342, 343, 344, 345, 346]
},
{
    id: 345,
    question: 'What is 65 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['37','38','36','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [343, 344, 345, 346, 347]
},
{
    id: 346,
    question: 'What is 65 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['37','33','38','35'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [344, 345, 346, 347, 348]
},
{
    id: 347,
    question: 'What is 65 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['34','32','36','31'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [345, 346, 347, 348, 349]
},
{
    id: 348,
    question: 'What is 65 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['34','31','33','32'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [346, 347, 348, 349, 350]
},
{
    id: 349,
    question: 'What is 65 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['32','29','34','31'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [347, 348, 349, 350, 351]
},
{
    id: 350,
    question: 'What is 65 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['28','33','31','29'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [348, 349, 350, 351, 352]
},
{
    id: 351,
    question: 'What is 65 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['30','32','28','27'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [349, 350, 351, 352, 353]
},
{
    id: 352,
    question: 'What is 65 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','27','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [350, 351, 352, 353, 354]
},
{
    id: 353,
    question: 'What is 65 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['29','26','25','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [351, 352, 353, 354, 355]
},
{
    id: 354,
    question: 'What is 65 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['29','30','25','27'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [352, 353, 354, 355, 356]
},
{
    id: 355,
    question: 'What is 65 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['28','27','23','26'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [353, 354, 355, 356, 357]
},
{
    id: 356,
    question: 'What is 65 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['25','22','24','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [354, 355, 356, 357, 358]
},
{
    id: 357,
    question: 'What is 65 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['25','24','27','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [355, 356, 357, 358, 359]
},
{
    id: 358,
    question: 'What is 65 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['24','25','23','26'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [356, 357, 358, 359, 360]
},
{
    id: 359,
    question: 'What is 65 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['19','22','24','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [357, 358, 359, 360, 361]
},
{
    id: 360,
    question: 'What is 65 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['21','23','19','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [358, 359, 360, 361, 362]
},
{
    id: 361,
    question: 'What is 65 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['20','18','21','17'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [359, 360, 361, 362, 363]
},
{
    id: 362,
    question: 'What is 65 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['20','16','19','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [360, 361, 362, 363, 364]
},
{
    id: 363,
    question: 'What is 65 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['16','18','20','19'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [361, 362, 363, 364, 365]
},
{
    id: 364,
    question: 'What is 65 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['14','18','15','17'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [362, 363, 364, 365, 366]
},
{
    id: 365,
    question: 'What is 65 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['15','13','14','16'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [363, 364, 365, 366, 367]
},
{
    id: 366,
    question: 'What is 65 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['18','15','14','13'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [364, 365, 366, 367, 368]
},
{
    id: 367,
    question: 'What is 65 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['15','16','14','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [365, 366, 367, 368, 369]
},
{
    id: 368,
    question: 'What is 65 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['13','15','16','11'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [366, 367, 368, 369, 370]
},
{
    id: 369,
    question: 'What is 65 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['12','10','9','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [367, 368, 369, 370, 371]
},
{
    id: 370,
    question: 'What is 65 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['8','11','10','9'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [368, 369, 370, 371, 372]
},
{
    id: 371,
    question: 'What is 65 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['12','10','8','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [369, 370, 371, 372, 373]
},
{
    id: 372,
    question: 'What is 65 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['10','11','9','8'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [370, 371, 372, 373, 374]
},
{
    id: 373,
    question: 'What is 65 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['9','5','8','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [371, 372, 373, 374, 375]
},
{
    id: 374,
    question: 'What is 65 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['7','10','4','6'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [372, 373, 374, 375, 376]
},
{
    id: 375,
    question: 'What is 65 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['5','3','6','7'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [373, 374, 375, 376, 377]
},
{
    id: 376,
    question: 'What is 65 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['5','6','2','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [374, 375, 376, 377, 378]
},
{
    id: 377,
    question: 'What is 65 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['4','2','1','6'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [375, 376, 377, 378, 379]
},
{
    id: 378,
    question: 'What is 65 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [376, 377, 378, 379, 380]
},
{
    id: 379,
    question: 'What is 65 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [377, 378, 379, 380, 381]
},
{
    id: 380,
    question: 'What is 65 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['1','2','0','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [378, 379, 380, 381, 382]
},
{
    id: 381,
    question: 'What is 65 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['1','2','0','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [381, 380, 382, 383, 384]
},
{
    id: 382,
    question: 'What is 66 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['66','63','65','67'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [380, 381, 382, 383, 384]
},
{
    id: 383,
    question: 'What is 66 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['64','68','62','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [381, 382, 383, 384, 385]
},
{
    id: 384,
    question: 'What is 66 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['61','65','64','66'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [382, 383, 384, 385, 386]
},
{
    id: 385,
    question: 'What is 66 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['64','60','63','66'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [383, 384, 385, 386, 387]
},
{
    id: 386,
    question: 'What is 66 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['65','59','62','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [384, 385, 386, 387, 388]
},
{
    id: 387,
    question: 'What is 66 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['63','64','59','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [385, 386, 387, 388, 389]
},
{
    id: 388,
    question: 'What is 66 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['63','62','61','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [386, 387, 388, 389, 390]
},
{
    id: 389,
    question: 'What is 66 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['60','61','58','59'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [387, 388, 389, 390, 391]
},
{
    id: 390,
    question: 'What is 66 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['58','61','60','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [388, 389, 390, 391, 392]
},
{
    id: 391,
    question: 'What is 66 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['57','59','60','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [391, 392, 390, 389, 388]
},
{
    id: 392,
    question: 'What is 66 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['53','56','57','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [390, 391, 392, 393, 394]
},
{
    id: 393,
    question: 'What is 66 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['57','55','58','52'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [391, 392, 393, 394, 395]
},
{
    id: 394,
    question: 'What is 66 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['51','57','54','55'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [392, 393, 394, 395, 396]
},
{
    id: 395,
    question: 'What is 66 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['56','51','53','55'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [393, 394, 395, 396, 397]
},
{
    id: 396,
    question: 'What is 66 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['54','52','53','51'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [394, 395, 396, 397, 398]
},
{
    id: 397,
    question: 'What is 66 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['50','53','49','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [395, 396, 397, 398, 399]
},
{
    id: 398,
    question: 'What is 66 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['51','47','50','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [396, 397, 398, 399, 400]
},
{
    id: 399,
    question: 'What is 66 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['50','52','49','51'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [397, 398, 399, 400, 401]
},
{
    id: 400,
    question: 'What is 66 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['46','47','51','48'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [398, 399, 400, 401, 402]
},
{
    id: 401,
    question: 'What is 66 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['50','44','47','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [399, 400, 401, 402, 403]
},
{
    id: 402,
    question: 'What is 66 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['46','47','49','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [400, 401, 402, 403, 404]
},
{
    id: 403,
    question: 'What is 66 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['46','43','45','47'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [401, 402, 403, 404, 405]
},
{
    id: 404,
    question: 'What is 66 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['43','41','44','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [402, 403, 404, 405, 406]
},
{
    id: 405,
    question: 'What is 66 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['43','46','44','41'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [403, 404, 405, 406, 407]
},
{
    id: 406,
    question: 'What is 66 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['39','42','40','44'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [404, 405, 406, 407, 408]
},
{
    id: 407,
    question: 'What is 66 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['38','41','39','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [405, 406, 407, 408, 409]
},
{
    id: 408,
    question: 'What is 66 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['37','40','38','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [406, 407, 408, 409, 410]
},
{
    id: 409,
    question: 'What is 66 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['38','41','37','39'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [407, 408, 409, 410, 411]
},
{
    id: 410,
    question: 'What is 66 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['36','41','35','38'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [408, 409, 410, 411, 412]
},
{
    id: 411,
    question: 'What is 66 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['40','37','36','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [409, 410, 411, 412, 413]
},
{
    id: 412,
    question: 'What is 66 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['37','38','36','35'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [410, 411, 412, 413, 414]
},
{
    id: 413,
    question: 'What is 66 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['33','34','32','35'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [411, 412, 413, 414, 415]
},
{
    id: 414,
    question: 'What is 66 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['35','37','32','34'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [412, 413, 414, 415, 416]
},
{
    id: 415,
    question: 'What is 66 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['30','35','33','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [413, 414, 415, 416, 417]
},
{
    id: 416,
    question: 'What is 66 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['29','30','32','35'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [414, 415, 416, 417, 418]
},
{
    id: 417,
    question: 'What is 66 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['31','33','32','30'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [415, 416, 417, 418, 419]
},
{
    id: 418,
    question: 'What is 66 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['33','30','29','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [416, 417, 418, 419, 420]
},
{
    id: 419,
    question: 'What is 66 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['29','31','27','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [417, 418, 419, 420, 421]
},
{
    id: 420,
    question: 'What is 66 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['29','28','26','30'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [418, 419, 420, 421, 422]
},
{
    id: 421,
    question: 'What is 66 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['30','27','28','26'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [419, 420, 421, 422, 423]
},
{
    id: 422,
    question: 'What is 66 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['23','28','24','26'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [420, 421, 422, 423, 424]
},
{
    id: 423,
    question: 'What is 66 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['26','23','25','28'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [421, 422, 423, 424, 425]
},
{
    id: 424,
    question: 'What is 66 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['21','25','22','24'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [422, 423, 424, 425, 426]
},
{
    id: 425,
    question: 'What is 66 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['20','24','23','21'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [423, 424, 425, 426, 427]
},
{
    id: 426,
    question: 'What is 66 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['24','21','23','22'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [424, 425, 426, 427, 428]
},
{
    id: 427,
    question: 'What is 66 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['22','21','18','19'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [425, 426, 427, 428, 429]
},
{
    id: 428,
    question: 'What is 66 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['18','19','20','22'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [426, 427, 428, 429, 430]
},
{
    id: 429,
    question: 'What is 66 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['22','19','18','16'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [427, 428, 429, 430, 431]
},
{
    id: 430,
    question: 'What is 66 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['21','16','18','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [428, 429, 430, 431, 432]
},
{
    id: 431,
    question: 'What is 66 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['17','16','15','19'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [429, 430, 431, 432, 433]
},
{
    id: 432,
    question: 'What is 66 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['14','13','15','16'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [430, 431, 432, 433, 434]
},
{
    id: 433,
    question: 'What is 66 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['13','12','15','14'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [431, 432, 433, 434, 435]
},
{
    id: 434,
    question: 'What is 66 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['13','16','15','14'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [432, 433, 434, 435, 436]
},
{
    id: 435,
    question: 'What is 66 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['12','13','11','16'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [433, 434, 435, 436, 437]
},
{
    id: 436,
    question: 'What is 66 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['13','14','12','15'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [434, 435, 436, 437, 438]
},
{
    id: 437,
    question: 'What is 66 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['11','8','9','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [435, 436, 437, 438, 439]
},
{
    id: 438,
    question: 'What is 66 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['10','9','8','7'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [436, 437, 438, 439, 440]
},
{
    id: 439,
    question: 'What is 66 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['12','9','10','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [437, 438, 439, 440, 441]
},
{
    id: 440,
    question: 'What is 66 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['9','8','5','10'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [438, 439, 440, 441, 442]
},
{
    id: 441,
    question: 'What is 66 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['7','5','10','9'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [439, 440, 441, 442, 443]
},
{
    id: 442,
    question: 'What is 66 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['8','9','6','7'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [440, 441, 442, 443, 444]
},
{
    id: 443,
    question: 'What is 66 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['8','7','5','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [441, 442, 443, 444, 445]
},
{
    id: 444,
    question: 'What is 66 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['7','4','3','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [442, 443, 444, 445, 446]
},
{
    id: 445,
    question: 'What is 66 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [443, 444, 445, 446, 447]
},
{
    id: 446,
    question: 'What is 66 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','0','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [444, 445, 446, 447, 448]
},
{
    id: 447,
    question: 'What is 66 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['0','2','1','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [445, 446, 447, 448, 449]
},
{
    id: 448,
    question: 'What is 66 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [448, 447, 449, 450, 451]
},
{
    id: 449,
    question: 'What is 67 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['67','68','66','69'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [447, 448, 449, 450, 451]
},
{
    id: 450,
    question: 'What is 67 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['67','66','69','68'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [448, 449, 450, 451, 452]
},
{
    id: 451,
    question: 'What is 67 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['65','66','67','68'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [449, 450, 451, 452, 453]
},
{
    id: 452,
    question: 'What is 67 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['65','67','62','64'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [450, 451, 452, 453, 454]
},
{
    id: 453,
    question: 'What is 67 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['64','61','63','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [451, 452, 453, 454, 455]
},
{
    id: 454,
    question: 'What is 67 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['64','59','62','63'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [452, 453, 454, 455, 456]
},
{
    id: 455,
    question: 'What is 67 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['59','62','60','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [453, 454, 455, 456, 457]
},
{
    id: 456,
    question: 'What is 67 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['59','62','58','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [454, 455, 456, 457, 458]
},
{
    id: 457,
    question: 'What is 67 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['57','61','59','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [455, 456, 457, 458, 459]
},
{
    id: 458,
    question: 'What is 67 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['60','59','58','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [458, 459, 457, 456, 455]
},
{
    id: 459,
    question: 'What is 67 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['55','60','57','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [457, 458, 459, 460, 461]
},
{
    id: 460,
    question: 'What is 67 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['59','54','56','55'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [458, 459, 460, 461, 462]
},
{
    id: 461,
    question: 'What is 67 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['53','52','57','55'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [459, 460, 461, 462, 463]
},
{
    id: 462,
    question: 'What is 67 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['52','55','54','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [460, 461, 462, 463, 464]
},
{
    id: 463,
    question: 'What is 67 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['51','53','55','56'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [461, 462, 463, 464, 465]
},
{
    id: 464,
    question: 'What is 67 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['50','51','54','52'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [462, 463, 464, 465, 466]
},
{
    id: 465,
    question: 'What is 67 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['51','54','52','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [463, 464, 465, 466, 467]
},
{
    id: 466,
    question: 'What is 67 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['50','47','49','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [464, 465, 466, 467, 468]
},
{
    id: 467,
    question: 'What is 67 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['46','49','48','47'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [465, 466, 467, 468, 469]
},
{
    id: 468,
    question: 'What is 67 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['51','50','48','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [466, 467, 468, 469, 470]
},
{
    id: 469,
    question: 'What is 67 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','45','50'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [467, 468, 469, 470, 471]
},
{
    id: 470,
    question: 'What is 67 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['48','46','49','47'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [468, 469, 470, 471, 472]
},
{
    id: 471,
    question: 'What is 67 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['48','47','45','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [469, 470, 471, 472, 473]
},
{
    id: 472,
    question: 'What is 67 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['45','47','44','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [470, 471, 472, 473, 474]
},
{
    id: 473,
    question: 'What is 67 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['40','42','41','43'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [471, 472, 473, 474, 475]
},
{
    id: 474,
    question: 'What is 67 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['42','44','40','39'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [472, 473, 474, 475, 476]
},
{
    id: 475,
    question: 'What is 67 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['39','41','43','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [473, 474, 475, 476, 477]
},
{
    id: 476,
    question: 'What is 67 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['37','43','39','40'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [474, 475, 476, 477, 478]
},
{
    id: 477,
    question: 'What is 67 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['39','40','38','36'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [475, 476, 477, 478, 479]
},
{
    id: 478,
    question: 'What is 67 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['35','41','38','37'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [476, 477, 478, 479, 480]
},
{
    id: 479,
    question: 'What is 67 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','39','34'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [477, 478, 479, 480, 481]
},
{
    id: 480,
    question: 'What is 67 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['34','35','36','33'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [478, 479, 480, 481, 482]
},
{
    id: 481,
    question: 'What is 67 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','37','36'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [479, 480, 481, 482, 483]
},
{
    id: 482,
    question: 'What is 67 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['37','35','36','34'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [480, 481, 482, 483, 484]
},
{
    id: 483,
    question: 'What is 67 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['30','34','33','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [481, 482, 483, 484, 485]
},
{
    id: 484,
    question: 'What is 67 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','34','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [482, 483, 484, 485, 486]
},
{
    id: 485,
    question: 'What is 67 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['33','31','32','34'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [483, 484, 485, 486, 487]
},
{
    id: 486,
    question: 'What is 67 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['30','28','27','31'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [484, 485, 486, 487, 488]
},
{
    id: 487,
    question: 'What is 67 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['28','32','27','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [485, 486, 487, 488, 489]
},
{
    id: 488,
    question: 'What is 67 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['29','27','31','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [486, 487, 488, 489, 490]
},
{
    id: 489,
    question: 'What is 67 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['27','25','24','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [487, 488, 489, 490, 491]
},
{
    id: 490,
    question: 'What is 67 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','26','27'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [488, 489, 490, 491, 492]
},
{
    id: 491,
    question: 'What is 67 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['28','22','25','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [489, 490, 491, 492, 493]
},
{
    id: 492,
    question: 'What is 67 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['24','27','21','25'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [490, 491, 492, 493, 494]
},
{
    id: 493,
    question: 'What is 67 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['22','21','26','23'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [491, 492, 493, 494, 495]
},
{
    id: 494,
    question: 'What is 67 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['21','23','25','22'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [492, 493, 494, 495, 496]
},
{
    id: 495,
    question: 'What is 67 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['20','19','21','18'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [493, 494, 495, 496, 497]
},
{
    id: 496,
    question: 'What is 67 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['20','21','22','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [494, 495, 496, 497, 498]
},
{
    id: 497,
    question: 'What is 67 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['16','17','21','19'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [495, 496, 497, 498, 499]
},
{
    id: 498,
    question: 'What is 67 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['16','21','20','18'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [496, 497, 498, 499, 500]
},
{
    id: 499,
    question: 'What is 67 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['14','17','15','16'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [497, 498, 499, 500, 501]
},
{
    id: 500,
    question: 'What is 67 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['16','13','15','14'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [498, 499, 500, 501, 502]
},
{
    id: 501,
    question: 'What is 67 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['13','18','16','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [499, 500, 501, 502, 503]
},
{
    id: 502,
    question: 'What is 67 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['15','16','13','14'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [500, 501, 502, 503, 504]
},
{
    id: 503,
    question: 'What is 67 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['13','11','12','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [501, 502, 503, 504, 505]
},
{
    id: 504,
    question: 'What is 67 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['10','11','12','9'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [502, 503, 504, 505, 506]
},
{
    id: 505,
    question: 'What is 67 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['12','11','14','9'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [503, 504, 505, 506, 507]
},
{
    id: 506,
    question: 'What is 67 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['9','10','12','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [504, 505, 506, 507, 508]
},
{
    id: 507,
    question: 'What is 67 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['12','11','10','9'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [505, 506, 507, 508, 509]
},
{
    id: 508,
    question: 'What is 67 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['8','5','6','7'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [506, 507, 508, 509, 510]
},
{
    id: 509,
    question: 'What is 67 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['8','5','7','6'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [507, 508, 509, 510, 511]
},
{
    id: 510,
    question: 'What is 67 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['4','3','7','6'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [508, 509, 510, 511, 512]
},
{
    id: 511,
    question: 'What is 67 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['3','5','2','7'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [509, 510, 511, 512, 513]
},
{
    id: 512,
    question: 'What is 67 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','2','4'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [510, 511, 512, 513, 514]
},
{
    id: 513,
    question: 'What is 67 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [511, 512, 513, 514, 515]
},
{
    id: 514,
    question: 'What is 67 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['0','2','3','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [512, 513, 514, 515, 516]
},
{
    id: 515,
    question: 'What is 67 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','1','0'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [513, 514, 515, 516, 517]
},
{
    id: 516,
    question: 'What is 67 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [516, 515, 517, 518, 519]
},
{
    id: 517,
    question: 'What is 68 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['65','71','67','68'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [515, 516, 517, 518, 519]
},
{
    id: 518,
    question: 'What is 68 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['66','64','67','69'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [516, 517, 518, 519, 520]
},
{
    id: 519,
    question: 'What is 68 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['63','67','66','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [517, 518, 519, 520, 521]
},
{
    id: 520,
    question: 'What is 68 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['67','66','65','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [518, 519, 520, 521, 522]
},
{
    id: 521,
    question: 'What is 68 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['63','66','65','64'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [519, 520, 521, 522, 523]
},
{
    id: 522,
    question: 'What is 68 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['61','60','63','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [520, 521, 522, 523, 524]
},
{
    id: 523,
    question: 'What is 68 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['63','64','62','60'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [521, 522, 523, 524, 525]
},
{
    id: 524,
    question: 'What is 68 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['59','58','61','60'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [522, 523, 524, 525, 526]
},
{
    id: 525,
    question: 'What is 68 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['60','63','62','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [523, 524, 525, 526, 527]
},
{
    id: 526,
    question: 'What is 68 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['59','56','60','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [526, 527, 525, 524, 523]
},
{
    id: 527,
    question: 'What is 68 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['58','60','57','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [525, 526, 527, 528, 529]
},
{
    id: 528,
    question: 'What is 68 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['55','54','60','57'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [526, 527, 528, 529, 530]
},
{
    id: 529,
    question: 'What is 68 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['55','54','56','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [527, 528, 529, 530, 531]
},
{
    id: 530,
    question: 'What is 68 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['53','55','54','52'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [528, 529, 530, 531, 532]
},
{
    id: 531,
    question: 'What is 68 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['57','51','56','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [529, 530, 531, 532, 533]
},
{
    id: 532,
    question: 'What is 68 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['51','53','55','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [530, 531, 532, 533, 534]
},
{
    id: 533,
    question: 'What is 68 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['50','55','52','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [531, 532, 533, 534, 535]
},
{
    id: 534,
    question: 'What is 68 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['53','50','51','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [532, 533, 534, 535, 536]
},
{
    id: 535,
    question: 'What is 68 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['50','48','52','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [533, 534, 535, 536, 537]
},
{
    id: 536,
    question: 'What is 68 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['48','46','49','51'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [534, 535, 536, 537, 538]
},
{
    id: 537,
    question: 'What is 68 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['48','45','46','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [535, 536, 537, 538, 539]
},
{
    id: 538,
    question: 'What is 68 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['50','47','48','46'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [536, 537, 538, 539, 540]
},
{
    id: 539,
    question: 'What is 68 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['46','49','44','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [537, 538, 539, 540, 541]
},
{
    id: 540,
    question: 'What is 68 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['44','42','46','45'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [538, 539, 540, 541, 542]
},
{
    id: 541,
    question: 'What is 68 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['43','47','44','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [539, 540, 541, 542, 543]
},
{
    id: 542,
    question: 'What is 68 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['44','40','43','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [540, 541, 542, 543, 544]
},
{
    id: 543,
    question: 'What is 68 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['41','44','43','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [541, 542, 543, 544, 545]
},
{
    id: 544,
    question: 'What is 68 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['38','39','44','41'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [542, 543, 544, 545, 546]
},
{
    id: 545,
    question: 'What is 68 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['38','43','40','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [543, 544, 545, 546, 547]
},
{
    id: 546,
    question: 'What is 68 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['39','40','41','42'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [544, 545, 546, 547, 548]
},
{
    id: 547,
    question: 'What is 68 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['39','40','38','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [545, 546, 547, 548, 549]
},
{
    id: 548,
    question: 'What is 68 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','35','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [546, 547, 548, 549, 550]
},
{
    id: 549,
    question: 'What is 68 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','35','34'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [547, 548, 549, 550, 551]
},
{
    id: 550,
    question: 'What is 68 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['35','38','34','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [548, 549, 550, 551, 552]
},
{
    id: 551,
    question: 'What is 68 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['34','36','32','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [549, 550, 551, 552, 553]
},
{
    id: 552,
    question: 'What is 68 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['33','36','31','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [550, 551, 552, 553, 554]
},
{
    id: 553,
    question: 'What is 68 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','30','31'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [551, 552, 553, 554, 555]
},
{
    id: 554,
    question: 'What is 68 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','30','33'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [552, 553, 554, 555, 556]
},
{
    id: 555,
    question: 'What is 68 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['33','31','30','29'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [553, 554, 555, 556, 557]
},
{
    id: 556,
    question: 'What is 68 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['30','26','27','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [554, 555, 556, 557, 558]
},
{
    id: 557,
    question: 'What is 68 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['31','29','27','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [555, 556, 557, 558, 559]
},
{
    id: 558,
    question: 'What is 68 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['27','28','25','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [556, 557, 558, 559, 560]
},
{
    id: 559,
    question: 'What is 68 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['26','28','29','25'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [557, 558, 559, 560, 561]
},
{
    id: 560,
    question: 'What is 68 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','26','23'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [558, 559, 560, 561, 562]
},
{
    id: 561,
    question: 'What is 68 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['24','27','22','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [559, 560, 561, 562, 563]
},
{
    id: 562,
    question: 'What is 68 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['23','26','22','20'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [560, 561, 562, 563, 564]
},
{
    id: 563,
    question: 'What is 68 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['25','24','20','22'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [561, 562, 563, 564, 565]
},
{
    id: 564,
    question: 'What is 68 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['24','23','22','21'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [562, 563, 564, 565, 566]
},
{
    id: 565,
    question: 'What is 68 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['20','19','17','21'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [563, 564, 565, 566, 567]
},
{
    id: 566,
    question: 'What is 68 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['19','17','22','20'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [564, 565, 566, 567, 568]
},
{
    id: 567,
    question: 'What is 68 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','21','17'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [565, 566, 567, 568, 569]
},
{
    id: 568,
    question: 'What is 68 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['16','19','15','17'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [566, 567, 568, 569, 570]
},
{
    id: 569,
    question: 'What is 68 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['18','16','15','13'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [567, 568, 569, 570, 571]
},
{
    id: 570,
    question: 'What is 68 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['12','16','15','14'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [568, 569, 570, 571, 572]
},
{
    id: 571,
    question: 'What is 68 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['15','17','12','14'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [569, 570, 571, 572, 573]
},
{
    id: 572,
    question: 'What is 68 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['15','13','11','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [570, 571, 572, 573, 574]
},
{
    id: 573,
    question: 'What is 68 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['10','13','9','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [571, 572, 573, 574, 575]
},
{
    id: 574,
    question: 'What is 68 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['11','8','9','14'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [572, 573, 574, 575, 576]
},
{
    id: 575,
    question: 'What is 68 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['10','9','11','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [573, 574, 575, 576, 577]
},
{
    id: 576,
    question: 'What is 68 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['9','6','10','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [574, 575, 576, 577, 578]
},
{
    id: 577,
    question: 'What is 68 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['9','8','11','7'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [575, 576, 577, 578, 579]
},
{
    id: 578,
    question: 'What is 68 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['4','5','7','6'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [576, 577, 578, 579, 580]
},
{
    id: 579,
    question: 'What is 68 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['3','7','6','9'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [577, 578, 579, 580, 581]
},
{
    id: 580,
    question: 'What is 68 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['6','3','8','5'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [578, 579, 580, 581, 582]
},
{
    id: 581,
    question: 'What is 68 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['3','4','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [579, 580, 581, 582, 583]
},
{
    id: 582,
    question: 'What is 68 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['2','3','0','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [580, 581, 582, 583, 584]
},
{
    id: 583,
    question: 'What is 68 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [581, 582, 583, 584, 585]
},
{
    id: 584,
    question: 'What is 68 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [582, 583, 584, 585, 586]
},
{
    id: 585,
    question: 'What is 68 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','2','0'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [585, 584, 586, 587, 588]
},
{
    id: 586,
    question: 'What is 69 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['70','69','72','71'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [584, 585, 586, 587, 588]
},
{
    id: 587,
    question: 'What is 69 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['70','66','68','65'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [585, 586, 587, 588, 589]
},
{
    id: 588,
    question: 'What is 69 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['67','64','66','65'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [586, 587, 588, 589, 590]
},
{
    id: 589,
    question: 'What is 69 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['66','65','64','63'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [587, 588, 589, 590, 591]
},
{
    id: 590,
    question: 'What is 69 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['68','63','64','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [588, 589, 590, 591, 592]
},
{
    id: 591,
    question: 'What is 69 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['62','67','61','64'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [589, 590, 591, 592, 593]
},
{
    id: 592,
    question: 'What is 69 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['60','61','63','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [590, 591, 592, 593, 594]
},
{
    id: 593,
    question: 'What is 69 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['65','64','61','62'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [591, 592, 593, 594, 595]
},
{
    id: 594,
    question: 'What is 69 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['64','63','61','60'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [592, 593, 594, 595, 596]
},
{
    id: 595,
    question: 'What is 69 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['62','57','59','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [595, 596, 594, 593, 592]
},
{
    id: 596,
    question: 'What is 69 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['62','60','59','61'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [594, 595, 596, 597, 598]
},
{
    id: 597,
    question: 'What is 69 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['55','60','58','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [595, 596, 597, 598, 599]
},
{
    id: 598,
    question: 'What is 69 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['55','57','58','59'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [596, 597, 598, 599, 600]
},
{
    id: 599,
    question: 'What is 69 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['54','56','59','58'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [597, 598, 599, 600, 601]
},
{
    id: 600,
    question: 'What is 69 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['56','57','55','58'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [598, 599, 600, 601, 602]
},
{
    id: 601,
    question: 'What is 69 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['56','54','55','53'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [599, 600, 601, 602, 603]
},
{
    id: 602,
    question: 'What is 69 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['51','50','52','53'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [600, 601, 602, 603, 604]
},
{
    id: 603,
    question: 'What is 69 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['54','51','55','52'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [601, 602, 603, 604, 605]
},
{
    id: 604,
    question: 'What is 69 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['51','48','50','54'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [602, 603, 604, 605, 606]
},
{
    id: 605,
    question: 'What is 69 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['48','47','49','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [603, 604, 605, 606, 607]
},
{
    id: 606,
    question: 'What is 69 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['47','46','49','52'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [604, 605, 606, 607, 608]
},
{
    id: 607,
    question: 'What is 69 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','51','48'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [605, 606, 607, 608, 609]
},
{
    id: 608,
    question: 'What is 69 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['45','47','48','44'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [606, 607, 608, 609, 610]
},
{
    id: 609,
    question: 'What is 69 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['47','46','45','44'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [607, 608, 609, 610, 611]
},
{
    id: 610,
    question: 'What is 69 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['47','43','42','45'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [608, 609, 610, 611, 612]
},
{
    id: 611,
    question: 'What is 69 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['44','46','47','45'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [609, 610, 611, 612, 613]
},
{
    id: 612,
    question: 'What is 69 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['45','41','43','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [610, 611, 612, 613, 614]
},
{
    id: 613,
    question: 'What is 69 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['41','45','44','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [611, 612, 613, 614, 615]
},
{
    id: 614,
    question: 'What is 69 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['44','38','40','41'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [612, 613, 614, 615, 616]
},
{
    id: 615,
    question: 'What is 69 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['43','41','40','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [613, 614, 615, 616, 617]
},
{
    id: 616,
    question: 'What is 69 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['36','38','37','39'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [614, 615, 616, 617, 618]
},
{
    id: 617,
    question: 'What is 69 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['39','37','35','38'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [615, 616, 617, 618, 619]
},
{
    id: 618,
    question: 'What is 69 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['37','34','39','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [616, 617, 618, 619, 620]
},
{
    id: 619,
    question: 'What is 69 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['39','36','33','38'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [617, 618, 619, 620, 621]
},
{
    id: 620,
    question: 'What is 69 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','33','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [618, 619, 620, 621, 622]
},
{
    id: 621,
    question: 'What is 69 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['34','31','37','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [619, 620, 621, 622, 623]
},
{
    id: 622,
    question: 'What is 69 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['35','31','33','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [620, 621, 622, 623, 624]
},
{
    id: 623,
    question: 'What is 69 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','31','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [621, 622, 623, 624, 625]
},
{
    id: 624,
    question: 'What is 69 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['33','28','34','31'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [622, 623, 624, 625, 626]
},
{
    id: 625,
    question: 'What is 69 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['30','32','31','29'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [623, 624, 625, 626, 627]
},
{
    id: 626,
    question: 'What is 69 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['29','26','32','28'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [624, 625, 626, 627, 628]
},
{
    id: 627,
    question: 'What is 69 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['27','28','30','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [625, 626, 627, 628, 629]
},
{
    id: 628,
    question: 'What is 69 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['29','27','28','30'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [626, 627, 628, 629, 630]
},
{
    id: 629,
    question: 'What is 69 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['26','25','23','29'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [627, 628, 629, 630, 631]
},
{
    id: 630,
    question: 'What is 69 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['22','23','25','28'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [628, 629, 630, 631, 632]
},
{
    id: 631,
    question: 'What is 69 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['25','27','24','22'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [629, 630, 631, 632, 633]
},
{
    id: 632,
    question: 'What is 69 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['23','22','21','24'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [630, 631, 632, 633, 634]
},
{
    id: 633,
    question: 'What is 69 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['19','21','22','20'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [631, 632, 633, 634, 635]
},
{
    id: 634,
    question: 'What is 69 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','21','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [632, 633, 634, 635, 636]
},
{
    id: 635,
    question: 'What is 69 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['18','22','21','20'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [633, 634, 635, 636, 637]
},
{
    id: 636,
    question: 'What is 69 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['20','19','21','17'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [634, 635, 636, 637, 638]
},
{
    id: 637,
    question: 'What is 69 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['18','20','21','16'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [635, 636, 637, 638, 639]
},
{
    id: 638,
    question: 'What is 69 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['16','14','15','17'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [636, 637, 638, 639, 640]
},
{
    id: 639,
    question: 'What is 69 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['13','18','16','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [637, 638, 639, 640, 641]
},
{
    id: 640,
    question: 'What is 69 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['14','16','15','18'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [638, 639, 640, 641, 642]
},
{
    id: 641,
    question: 'What is 69 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['15','14','16','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [639, 640, 641, 642, 643]
},
{
    id: 642,
    question: 'What is 69 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['10','11','13','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [640, 641, 642, 643, 644]
},
{
    id: 643,
    question: 'What is 69 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['12','14','15','9'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [641, 642, 643, 644, 645]
},
{
    id: 644,
    question: 'What is 69 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['12','8','14','11'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [642, 643, 644, 645, 646]
},
{
    id: 645,
    question: 'What is 69 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['8','10','11','13'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [643, 644, 645, 646, 647]
},
{
    id: 646,
    question: 'What is 69 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['10','9','6','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [644, 645, 646, 647, 648]
},
{
    id: 647,
    question: 'What is 69 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['5','8','6','10'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [645, 646, 647, 648, 649]
},
{
    id: 648,
    question: 'What is 69 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['7','8','5','9'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [646, 647, 648, 649, 650]
},
{
    id: 649,
    question: 'What is 69 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['5','8','3','6'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [647, 648, 649, 650, 651]
},
{
    id: 650,
    question: 'What is 69 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['3','5','8','6'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [648, 649, 650, 651, 652]
},
{
    id: 651,
    question: 'What is 69 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['4','2','6','7'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [649, 650, 651, 652, 653]
},
{
    id: 652,
    question: 'What is 69 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','3','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [650, 651, 652, 653, 654]
},
{
    id: 653,
    question: 'What is 69 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [651, 652, 653, 654, 655]
},
{
    id: 654,
    question: 'What is 69 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['2','1','3','0'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [652, 653, 654, 655, 656]
},
{
    id: 655,
    question: 'What is 69 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','1','0'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [655, 654, 656, 657, 658]
},
{
    id: 656,
    question: 'What is 70 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['72','70','73','67'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [654, 655, 656, 657, 658]
},
{
    id: 657,
    question: 'What is 70 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['69','67','66','68'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [655, 656, 657, 658, 659]
},
{
    id: 658,
    question: 'What is 70 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['70','69','66','68'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [656, 657, 658, 659, 660]
},
{
    id: 659,
    question: 'What is 70 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['67','69','64','70'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [657, 658, 659, 660, 661]
},
{
    id: 660,
    question: 'What is 70 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['67','68','63','66'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [658, 659, 660, 661, 662]
},
{
    id: 661,
    question: 'What is 70 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['64','68','65','66'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [659, 660, 661, 662, 663]
},
{
    id: 662,
    question: 'What is 70 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['64','65','67','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [660, 661, 662, 663, 664]
},
{
    id: 663,
    question: 'What is 70 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['62','60','63','61'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [661, 662, 663, 664, 665]
},
{
    id: 664,
    question: 'What is 70 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['65','64','63','62'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [662, 663, 664, 665, 666]
},
{
    id: 665,
    question: 'What is 70 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['63','62','61','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [665, 666, 664, 663, 662]
},
{
    id: 666,
    question: 'What is 70 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['59','63','61','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [664, 665, 666, 667, 668]
},
{
    id: 667,
    question: 'What is 70 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['62','59','56','57'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [665, 666, 667, 668, 669]
},
{
    id: 668,
    question: 'What is 70 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['58','55','56','57'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [666, 667, 668, 669, 670]
},
{
    id: 669,
    question: 'What is 70 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['57','58','55','60'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [667, 668, 669, 670, 671]
},
{
    id: 670,
    question: 'What is 70 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['56','59','58','57'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [668, 669, 670, 671, 672]
},
{
    id: 671,
    question: 'What is 70 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['55','52','58','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [669, 670, 671, 672, 673]
},
{
    id: 672,
    question: 'What is 70 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['57','56','55','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [670, 671, 672, 673, 674]
},
{
    id: 673,
    question: 'What is 70 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['56','52','53','54'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [671, 672, 673, 674, 675]
},
{
    id: 674,
    question: 'What is 70 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['52','54','55','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [672, 673, 674, 675, 676]
},
{
    id: 675,
    question: 'What is 70 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['50','52','48','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [673, 674, 675, 676, 677]
},
{
    id: 676,
    question: 'What is 70 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['47','50','49','48'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [674, 675, 676, 677, 678]
},
{
    id: 677,
    question: 'What is 70 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['46','47','48','49'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [675, 676, 677, 678, 679]
},
{
    id: 678,
    question: 'What is 70 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['48','47','45','50'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [676, 677, 678, 679, 680]
},
{
    id: 679,
    question: 'What is 70 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['44','47','45','49'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [677, 678, 679, 680, 681]
},
{
    id: 680,
    question: 'What is 70 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['45','43','48','46'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [678, 679, 680, 681, 682]
},
{
    id: 681,
    question: 'What is 70 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['45','46','42','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [679, 680, 681, 682, 683]
},
{
    id: 682,
    question: 'What is 70 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['41','44','42','47'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [680, 681, 682, 683, 684]
},
{
    id: 683,
    question: 'What is 70 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['43','44','45','46'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [681, 682, 683, 684, 685]
},
{
    id: 684,
    question: 'What is 70 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['42','45','39','43'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [682, 683, 684, 685, 686]
},
{
    id: 685,
    question: 'What is 70 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['43','44','41','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [683, 684, 685, 686, 687]
},
{
    id: 686,
    question: 'What is 70 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['43','41','40','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [684, 685, 686, 687, 688]
},
{
    id: 687,
    question: 'What is 70 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['41','39','36','40'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [685, 686, 687, 688, 689]
},
{
    id: 688,
    question: 'What is 70 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['36','35','40','38'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [686, 687, 688, 689, 690]
},
{
    id: 689,
    question: 'What is 70 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['36','38','37','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [687, 688, 689, 690, 691]
},
{
    id: 690,
    question: 'What is 70 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','33','34'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [688, 689, 690, 691, 692]
},
{
    id: 691,
    question: 'What is 70 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','35','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [689, 690, 691, 692, 693]
},
{
    id: 692,
    question: 'What is 70 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['35','34','36','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [690, 691, 692, 693, 694]
},
{
    id: 693,
    question: 'What is 70 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['34','33','35','32'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [691, 692, 693, 694, 695]
},
{
    id: 694,
    question: 'What is 70 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['33','32','34','35'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [692, 693, 694, 695, 696]
},
{
    id: 695,
    question: 'What is 70 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['29','32','33','31'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [693, 694, 695, 696, 697]
},
{
    id: 696,
    question: 'What is 70 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['32','33','30','31'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [694, 695, 696, 697, 698]
},
{
    id: 697,
    question: 'What is 70 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['32','29','31','30'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [695, 696, 697, 698, 699]
},
{
    id: 698,
    question: 'What is 70 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['26','28','27','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [696, 697, 698, 699, 700]
},
{
    id: 699,
    question: 'What is 70 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['26','27','29','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [697, 698, 699, 700, 701]
},
{
    id: 700,
    question: 'What is 70 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['26','29','23','27'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [698, 699, 700, 701, 702]
},
{
    id: 701,
    question: 'What is 70 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['26','28','25','27'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [699, 700, 701, 702, 703]
},
{
    id: 702,
    question: 'What is 70 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['26','21','23','24'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [700, 701, 702, 703, 704]
},
{
    id: 703,
    question: 'What is 70 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['23','25','21','24'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [701, 702, 703, 704, 705]
},
{
    id: 704,
    question: 'What is 70 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['22','25','24','19'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [702, 703, 704, 705, 706]
},
{
    id: 705,
    question: 'What is 70 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['21','20','24','23'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [703, 704, 705, 706, 707]
},
{
    id: 706,
    question: 'What is 70 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['20','17','22','19'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [704, 705, 706, 707, 708]
},
{
    id: 707,
    question: 'What is 70 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['19','22','20','21'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [705, 706, 707, 708, 709]
},
{
    id: 708,
    question: 'What is 70 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['17','18','19','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [706, 707, 708, 709, 710]
},
{
    id: 709,
    question: 'What is 70 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['19','15','20','17'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [707, 708, 709, 710, 711]
},
{
    id: 710,
    question: 'What is 70 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','19','16'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [708, 709, 710, 711, 712]
},
{
    id: 711,
    question: 'What is 70 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['15','16','18','17'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [709, 710, 711, 712, 713]
},
{
    id: 712,
    question: 'What is 70 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['12','11','13','14'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [710, 711, 712, 713, 714]
},
{
    id: 713,
    question: 'What is 70 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['16','13','10','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [711, 712, 713, 714, 715]
},
{
    id: 714,
    question: 'What is 70 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','13','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [712, 713, 714, 715, 716]
},
{
    id: 715,
    question: 'What is 70 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['8','12','11','13'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [713, 714, 715, 716, 717]
},
{
    id: 716,
    question: 'What is 70 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','8','13'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [714, 715, 716, 717, 718]
},
{
    id: 717,
    question: 'What is 70 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['11','8','6','9'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [715, 716, 717, 718, 719]
},
{
    id: 718,
    question: 'What is 70 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['5','9','7','8'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [716, 717, 718, 719, 720]
},
{
    id: 719,
    question: 'What is 70 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['5','7','4','10'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [717, 718, 719, 720, 721]
},
{
    id: 720,
    question: 'What is 70 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['5','4','6','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [718, 719, 720, 721, 722]
},
{
    id: 721,
    question: 'What is 70 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['8','7','5','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [719, 720, 721, 722, 723]
},
{
    id: 722,
    question: 'What is 70 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['3','6','2','4'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [720, 721, 722, 723, 724]
},
{
    id: 723,
    question: 'What is 70 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [721, 722, 723, 724, 725]
},
{
    id: 724,
    question: 'What is 70 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [722, 723, 724, 725, 726]
},
{
    id: 725,
    question: 'What is 70 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [723, 724, 725, 726, 727]
},
{
    id: 726,
    question: 'What is 70 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','2','0'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [726, 725, 727, 728, 729]
},
{
    id: 727,
    question: 'What is 71 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['72','74','71','73'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [725, 726, 727, 728, 729]
},
{
    id: 728,
    question: 'What is 71 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['71','72','70','68'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [726, 727, 728, 729, 730]
},
{
    id: 729,
    question: 'What is 71 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['67','69','70','68'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [727, 728, 729, 730, 731]
},
{
    id: 730,
    question: 'What is 71 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['65','68','70','69'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [728, 729, 730, 731, 732]
},
{
    id: 731,
    question: 'What is 71 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['67','64','65','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [729, 730, 731, 732, 733]
},
{
    id: 732,
    question: 'What is 71 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['68','67','66','69'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [730, 731, 732, 733, 734]
},
{
    id: 733,
    question: 'What is 71 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['67','65','66','62'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [731, 732, 733, 734, 735]
},
{
    id: 734,
    question: 'What is 71 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['64','63','62','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [732, 733, 734, 735, 736]
},
{
    id: 735,
    question: 'What is 71 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['65','61','63','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [733, 734, 735, 736, 737]
},
{
    id: 736,
    question: 'What is 71 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['61','59','64','62'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [736, 737, 735, 734, 733]
},
{
    id: 737,
    question: 'What is 71 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['63','62','61','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [735, 736, 737, 738, 739]
},
{
    id: 738,
    question: 'What is 71 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['62','57','60','59'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [736, 737, 738, 739, 740]
},
{
    id: 739,
    question: 'What is 71 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['59','61','60','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [737, 738, 739, 740, 741]
},
{
    id: 740,
    question: 'What is 71 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['58','59','60','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [738, 739, 740, 741, 742]
},
{
    id: 741,
    question: 'What is 71 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['57','59','60','58'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [739, 740, 741, 742, 743]
},
{
    id: 742,
    question: 'What is 71 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['56','59','53','54'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [740, 741, 742, 743, 744]
},
{
    id: 743,
    question: 'What is 71 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['54','57','55','58'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [741, 742, 743, 744, 745]
},
{
    id: 744,
    question: 'What is 71 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['56','51','55','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [742, 743, 744, 745, 746]
},
{
    id: 745,
    question: 'What is 71 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['53','55','56','54'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [743, 744, 745, 746, 747]
},
{
    id: 746,
    question: 'What is 71 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['51','52','55','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [744, 745, 746, 747, 748]
},
{
    id: 747,
    question: 'What is 71 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['48','51','50','49'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [745, 746, 747, 748, 749]
},
{
    id: 748,
    question: 'What is 71 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['53','47','51','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [746, 747, 748, 749, 750]
},
{
    id: 749,
    question: 'What is 71 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['48','46','47','49'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [747, 748, 749, 750, 751]
},
{
    id: 750,
    question: 'What is 71 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['48','47','46','49'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [748, 749, 750, 751, 752]
},
{
    id: 751,
    question: 'What is 71 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['50','45','47','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [749, 750, 751, 752, 753]
},
{
    id: 752,
    question: 'What is 71 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['45','43','46','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [750, 751, 752, 753, 754]
},
{
    id: 753,
    question: 'What is 71 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['45','47','43','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [751, 752, 753, 754, 755]
},
{
    id: 754,
    question: 'What is 71 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['47','42','46','44'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [752, 753, 754, 755, 756]
},
{
    id: 755,
    question: 'What is 71 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['40','45','43','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [753, 754, 755, 756, 757]
},
{
    id: 756,
    question: 'What is 71 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['41','42','43','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [754, 755, 756, 757, 758]
},
{
    id: 757,
    question: 'What is 71 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['42','40','44','41'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [755, 756, 757, 758, 759]
},
{
    id: 758,
    question: 'What is 71 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['40','38','39','43'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [756, 757, 758, 759, 760]
},
{
    id: 759,
    question: 'What is 71 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['36','39','42','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [757, 758, 759, 760, 761]
},
{
    id: 760,
    question: 'What is 71 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['38','35','36','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [758, 759, 760, 761, 762]
},
{
    id: 761,
    question: 'What is 71 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['34','38','37','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [759, 760, 761, 762, 763]
},
{
    id: 762,
    question: 'What is 71 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['35','33','39','36'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [760, 761, 762, 763, 764]
},
{
    id: 763,
    question: 'What is 71 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['38','35','36','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [761, 762, 763, 764, 765]
},
{
    id: 764,
    question: 'What is 71 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['36','34','37','35'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [762, 763, 764, 765, 766]
},
{
    id: 765,
    question: 'What is 71 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['35','33','32','36'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [763, 764, 765, 766, 767]
},
{
    id: 766,
    question: 'What is 71 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['30','31','29','32'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [764, 765, 766, 767, 768]
},
{
    id: 767,
    question: 'What is 71 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['34','31','30','32'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [765, 766, 767, 768, 769]
},
{
    id: 768,
    question: 'What is 71 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['28','30','29','27'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [766, 767, 768, 769, 770]
},
{
    id: 769,
    question: 'What is 71 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['30','31','29','28'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [767, 768, 769, 770, 771]
},
{
    id: 770,
    question: 'What is 71 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['29','30','31','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [768, 769, 770, 771, 772]
},
{
    id: 771,
    question: 'What is 71 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['26','27','24','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [769, 770, 771, 772, 773]
},
{
    id: 772,
    question: 'What is 71 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['29','27','26','28'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [770, 771, 772, 773, 774]
},
{
    id: 773,
    question: 'What is 71 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['25','23','28','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [771, 772, 773, 774, 775]
},
{
    id: 774,
    question: 'What is 71 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['24','27','23','25'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [772, 773, 774, 775, 776]
},
{
    id: 775,
    question: 'What is 71 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['23','25','24','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [773, 774, 775, 776, 777]
},
{
    id: 776,
    question: 'What is 71 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['25','23','22','24'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [774, 775, 776, 777, 778]
},
{
    id: 777,
    question: 'What is 71 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['23','20','22','21'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [775, 776, 777, 778, 779]
},
{
    id: 778,
    question: 'What is 71 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['23','20','19','17'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [776, 777, 778, 779, 780]
},
{
    id: 779,
    question: 'What is 71 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['19','20','18','17'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [777, 778, 779, 780, 781]
},
{
    id: 780,
    question: 'What is 71 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','20','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [778, 779, 780, 781, 782]
},
{
    id: 781,
    question: 'What is 71 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['20','19','17','18'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [779, 780, 781, 782, 783]
},
{
    id: 782,
    question: 'What is 71 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['19','17','15','16'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [780, 781, 782, 783, 784]
},
{
    id: 783,
    question: 'What is 71 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['17','14','18','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [781, 782, 783, 784, 785]
},
{
    id: 784,
    question: 'What is 71 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['11','14','17','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [782, 783, 784, 785, 786]
},
{
    id: 785,
    question: 'What is 71 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['16','12','13','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [783, 784, 785, 786, 787]
},
{
    id: 786,
    question: 'What is 71 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','9','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [784, 785, 786, 787, 788]
},
{
    id: 787,
    question: 'What is 71 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['8','14','11','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [785, 786, 787, 788, 789]
},
{
    id: 788,
    question: 'What is 71 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['10','11','8','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [786, 787, 788, 789, 790]
},
{
    id: 789,
    question: 'What is 71 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['7','8','10','9'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [787, 788, 789, 790, 791]
},
{
    id: 790,
    question: 'What is 71 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['11','8','10','7'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [788, 789, 790, 791, 792]
},
{
    id: 791,
    question: 'What is 71 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['7','10','5','6'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [789, 790, 791, 792, 793]
},
{
    id: 792,
    question: 'What is 71 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['9','8','6','7'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [790, 791, 792, 793, 794]
},
{
    id: 793,
    question: 'What is 71 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['5','4','8','6'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [791, 792, 793, 794, 795]
},
{
    id: 794,
    question: 'What is 71 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['6','4','7','5'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [792, 793, 794, 795, 796]
},
{
    id: 795,
    question: 'What is 71 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [793, 794, 795, 796, 797]
},
{
    id: 796,
    question: 'What is 71 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [794, 795, 796, 797, 798]
},
{
    id: 797,
    question: 'What is 71 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [795, 796, 797, 798, 799]
},
{
    id: 798,
    question: 'What is 71 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['2','0','3','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [798, 797, 799, 800, 801]
},
{
    id: 799,
    question: 'What is 72 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['69','75','74','72'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [797, 798, 799, 800, 801]
},
{
    id: 800,
    question: 'What is 72 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['72','71','74','73'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [798, 799, 800, 801, 802]
},
{
    id: 801,
    question: 'What is 72 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['69','67','70','68'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [799, 800, 801, 802, 803]
},
{
    id: 802,
    question: 'What is 72 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['72','71','70','69'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [800, 801, 802, 803, 804]
},
{
    id: 803,
    question: 'What is 72 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['69','71','68','67'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [801, 802, 803, 804, 805]
},
{
    id: 804,
    question: 'What is 72 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['67','69','66','68'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [802, 803, 804, 805, 806]
},
{
    id: 805,
    question: 'What is 72 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['68','64','63','66'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [803, 804, 805, 806, 807]
},
{
    id: 806,
    question: 'What is 72 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['65','68','67','64'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [804, 805, 806, 807, 808]
},
{
    id: 807,
    question: 'What is 72 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['66','63','64','67'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [805, 806, 807, 808, 809]
},
{
    id: 808,
    question: 'What is 72 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['62','60','64','63'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [808, 809, 807, 806, 805]
},
{
    id: 809,
    question: 'What is 72 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['62','65','63','64'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [807, 808, 809, 810, 811]
},
{
    id: 810,
    question: 'What is 72 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['58','60','61','63'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [808, 809, 810, 811, 812]
},
{
    id: 811,
    question: 'What is 72 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['62','58','63','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [809, 810, 811, 812, 813]
},
{
    id: 812,
    question: 'What is 72 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['59','60','58','57'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [810, 811, 812, 813, 814]
},
{
    id: 813,
    question: 'What is 72 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['60','59','61','58'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [811, 812, 813, 814, 815]
},
{
    id: 814,
    question: 'What is 72 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['54','55','57','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [812, 813, 814, 815, 816]
},
{
    id: 815,
    question: 'What is 72 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['55','58','54','56'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [813, 814, 815, 816, 817]
},
{
    id: 816,
    question: 'What is 72 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['56','58','55','57'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [814, 815, 816, 817, 818]
},
{
    id: 817,
    question: 'What is 72 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['57','55','56','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [815, 816, 817, 818, 819]
},
{
    id: 818,
    question: 'What is 72 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['50','54','51','53'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [816, 817, 818, 819, 820]
},
{
    id: 819,
    question: 'What is 72 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['55','51','52','54'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [817, 818, 819, 820, 821]
},
{
    id: 820,
    question: 'What is 72 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['49','54','50','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [818, 819, 820, 821, 822]
},
{
    id: 821,
    question: 'What is 72 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','51','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [819, 820, 821, 822, 823]
},
{
    id: 822,
    question: 'What is 72 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['48','50','51','49'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [820, 821, 822, 823, 824]
},
{
    id: 823,
    question: 'What is 72 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['49','51','48','50'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [821, 822, 823, 824, 825]
},
{
    id: 824,
    question: 'What is 72 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['50','47','46','45'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [822, 823, 824, 825, 826]
},
{
    id: 825,
    question: 'What is 72 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['49','47','48','46'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [823, 824, 825, 826, 827]
},
{
    id: 826,
    question: 'What is 72 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['44','48','45','47'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [824, 825, 826, 827, 828]
},
{
    id: 827,
    question: 'What is 72 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['45','46','44','43'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [825, 826, 827, 828, 829]
},
{
    id: 828,
    question: 'What is 72 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['42','41','40','43'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [826, 827, 828, 829, 830]
},
{
    id: 829,
    question: 'What is 72 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['43','42','40','41'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [827, 828, 829, 830, 831]
},
{
    id: 830,
    question: 'What is 72 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['39','40','38','41'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [828, 829, 830, 831, 832]
},
{
    id: 831,
    question: 'What is 72 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['38','41','37','40'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [829, 830, 831, 832, 833]
},
{
    id: 832,
    question: 'What is 72 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['38','36','39','40'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [830, 831, 832, 833, 834]
},
{
    id: 833,
    question: 'What is 72 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','38','35'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [831, 832, 833, 834, 835]
},
{
    id: 834,
    question: 'What is 72 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['34','36','35','37'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [832, 833, 834, 835, 836]
},
{
    id: 835,
    question: 'What is 72 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['38','36','37','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [833, 834, 835, 836, 837]
},
{
    id: 836,
    question: 'What is 72 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','34','33'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [834, 835, 836, 837, 838]
},
{
    id: 837,
    question: 'What is 72 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['33','34','32','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [835, 836, 837, 838, 839]
},
{
    id: 838,
    question: 'What is 72 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['34','32','33','31'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [836, 837, 838, 839, 840]
},
{
    id: 839,
    question: 'What is 72 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['32','34','35','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [837, 838, 839, 840, 841]
},
{
    id: 840,
    question: 'What is 72 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['33','28','31','29'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [838, 839, 840, 841, 842]
},
{
    id: 841,
    question: 'What is 72 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['28','30','31','29'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [839, 840, 841, 842, 843]
},
{
    id: 842,
    question: 'What is 72 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['31','29','30','26'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [840, 841, 842, 843, 844]
},
{
    id: 843,
    question: 'What is 72 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['25','27','26','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [841, 842, 843, 844, 845]
},
{
    id: 844,
    question: 'What is 72 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['25','24','26','27'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [842, 843, 844, 845, 846]
},
{
    id: 845,
    question: 'What is 72 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['28','23','24','26'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [843, 844, 845, 846, 847]
},
{
    id: 846,
    question: 'What is 72 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['28','23','25','24'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [844, 845, 846, 847, 848]
},
{
    id: 847,
    question: 'What is 72 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','27','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [845, 846, 847, 848, 849]
},
{
    id: 848,
    question: 'What is 72 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['20','26','23','25'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [846, 847, 848, 849, 850]
},
{
    id: 849,
    question: 'What is 72 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','21','25'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [847, 848, 849, 850, 851]
},
{
    id: 850,
    question: 'What is 72 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['20','19','21','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [848, 849, 850, 851, 852]
},
{
    id: 851,
    question: 'What is 72 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['23','21','20','22'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [849, 850, 851, 852, 853]
},
{
    id: 852,
    question: 'What is 72 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['17','22','18','19'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [850, 851, 852, 853, 854]
},
{
    id: 853,
    question: 'What is 72 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['18','19','15','17'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [851, 852, 853, 854, 855]
},
{
    id: 854,
    question: 'What is 72 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['17','15','19','20'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [852, 853, 854, 855, 856]
},
{
    id: 855,
    question: 'What is 72 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['18','16','19','17'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [853, 854, 855, 856, 857]
},
{
    id: 856,
    question: 'What is 72 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['14','13','15','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [854, 855, 856, 857, 858]
},
{
    id: 857,
    question: 'What is 72 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['14','13','17','15'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [855, 856, 857, 858, 859]
},
{
    id: 858,
    question: 'What is 72 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['11','15','12','13'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [856, 857, 858, 859, 860]
},
{
    id: 859,
    question: 'What is 72 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['10','15','12','14'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [857, 858, 859, 860, 861]
},
{
    id: 860,
    question: 'What is 72 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['11','14','9','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [858, 859, 860, 861, 862]
},
{
    id: 861,
    question: 'What is 72 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['12','11','7','10'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [859, 860, 861, 862, 863]
},
{
    id: 862,
    question: 'What is 72 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['6','7','9','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [860, 861, 862, 863, 864]
},
{
    id: 863,
    question: 'What is 72 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['8','7','5','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [861, 862, 863, 864, 865]
},
{
    id: 864,
    question: 'What is 72 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['8','7','9','6'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [862, 863, 864, 865, 866]
},
{
    id: 865,
    question: 'What is 72 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['6','5','9','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [863, 864, 865, 866, 867]
},
{
    id: 866,
    question: 'What is 72 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['3','8','2','5'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [864, 865, 866, 867, 868]
},
{
    id: 867,
    question: 'What is 72 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['1','6','4','5'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [865, 866, 867, 868, 869]
},
{
    id: 868,
    question: 'What is 72 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [866, 867, 868, 869, 870]
},
{
    id: 869,
    question: 'What is 72 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [867, 868, 869, 870, 871]
},
{
    id: 870,
    question: 'What is 72 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [868, 869, 870, 871, 872]
},
{
    id: 871,
    question: 'What is 72 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['0','2','1','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [871, 870, 872, 873, 874]
},
{
    id: 872,
    question: 'What is 73 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['73','70','75','76'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [870, 871, 872, 873, 874]
},
{
    id: 873,
    question: 'What is 73 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['75','73','72','74'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [871, 872, 873, 874, 875]
},
{
    id: 874,
    question: 'What is 73 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['70','72','71','69'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [872, 873, 874, 875, 876]
},
{
    id: 875,
    question: 'What is 73 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['68','70','72','67'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [873, 874, 875, 876, 877]
},
{
    id: 876,
    question: 'What is 73 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['67','69','70','68'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [874, 875, 876, 877, 878]
},
{
    id: 877,
    question: 'What is 73 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['67','65','66','68'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [875, 876, 877, 878, 879]
},
{
    id: 878,
    question: 'What is 73 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['67','66','68','65'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [876, 877, 878, 879, 880]
},
{
    id: 879,
    question: 'What is 73 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['64','66','63','69'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [877, 878, 879, 880, 881]
},
{
    id: 880,
    question: 'What is 73 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['62','65','64','63'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [878, 879, 880, 881, 882]
},
{
    id: 881,
    question: 'What is 73 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['65','64','67','66'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [881, 882, 880, 879, 878]
},
{
    id: 882,
    question: 'What is 73 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['60','61','66','63'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [880, 881, 882, 883, 884]
},
{
    id: 883,
    question: 'What is 73 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['62','60','63','65'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [881, 882, 883, 884, 885]
},
{
    id: 884,
    question: 'What is 73 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['64','63','61','60'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [882, 883, 884, 885, 886]
},
{
    id: 885,
    question: 'What is 73 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['58','59','57','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [883, 884, 885, 886, 887]
},
{
    id: 886,
    question: 'What is 73 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['60','57','62','59'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [884, 885, 886, 887, 888]
},
{
    id: 887,
    question: 'What is 73 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['58','61','55','60'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [885, 886, 887, 888, 889]
},
{
    id: 888,
    question: 'What is 73 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['58','57','59','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [886, 887, 888, 889, 890]
},
{
    id: 889,
    question: 'What is 73 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['59','57','55','56'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [887, 888, 889, 890, 891]
},
{
    id: 890,
    question: 'What is 73 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['55','58','57','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [888, 889, 890, 891, 892]
},
{
    id: 891,
    question: 'What is 73 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['53','57','54','56'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [889, 890, 891, 892, 893]
},
{
    id: 892,
    question: 'What is 73 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['50','55','53','51'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [890, 891, 892, 893, 894]
},
{
    id: 893,
    question: 'What is 73 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['50','52','49','51'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [891, 892, 893, 894, 895]
},
{
    id: 894,
    question: 'What is 73 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['49','51','54','52'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [892, 893, 894, 895, 896]
},
{
    id: 895,
    question: 'What is 73 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['49','47','48','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [893, 894, 895, 896, 897]
},
{
    id: 896,
    question: 'What is 73 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['46','49','51','47'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [894, 895, 896, 897, 898]
},
{
    id: 897,
    question: 'What is 73 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['51','49','48','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [895, 896, 897, 898, 899]
},
{
    id: 898,
    question: 'What is 73 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['44','45','46','47'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [896, 897, 898, 899, 900]
},
{
    id: 899,
    question: 'What is 73 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['44','46','45','48'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [897, 898, 899, 900, 901]
},
{
    id: 900,
    question: 'What is 73 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['46','42','43','45'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [898, 899, 900, 901, 902]
},
{
    id: 901,
    question: 'What is 73 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['42','47','41','44'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [899, 900, 901, 902, 903]
},
{
    id: 902,
    question: 'What is 73 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['40','42','43','41'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [900, 901, 902, 903, 904]
},
{
    id: 903,
    question: 'What is 73 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['39','40','43','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [901, 902, 903, 904, 905]
},
{
    id: 904,
    question: 'What is 73 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['38','39','41','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [902, 903, 904, 905, 906]
},
{
    id: 905,
    question: 'What is 73 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['43','41','40','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [903, 904, 905, 906, 907]
},
{
    id: 906,
    question: 'What is 73 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['42','39','40','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [904, 905, 906, 907, 908]
},
{
    id: 907,
    question: 'What is 73 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['41','38','37','40'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [905, 906, 907, 908, 909]
},
{
    id: 908,
    question: 'What is 73 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['37','34','36','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [906, 907, 908, 909, 910]
},
{
    id: 909,
    question: 'What is 73 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['36','34','33','39'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [907, 908, 909, 910, 911]
},
{
    id: 910,
    question: 'What is 73 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['35','37','33','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [908, 909, 910, 911, 912]
},
{
    id: 911,
    question: 'What is 73 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['35','36','34','32'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [909, 910, 911, 912, 913]
},
{
    id: 912,
    question: 'What is 73 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['33','35','34','30'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [910, 911, 912, 913, 914]
},
{
    id: 913,
    question: 'What is 73 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['33','32','35','34'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [911, 912, 913, 914, 915]
},
{
    id: 914,
    question: 'What is 73 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['34','32','31','33'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [912, 913, 914, 915, 916]
},
{
    id: 915,
    question: 'What is 73 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['30','29','28','27'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [913, 914, 915, 916, 917]
},
{
    id: 916,
    question: 'What is 73 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['26','32','30','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [914, 915, 916, 917, 918]
},
{
    id: 917,
    question: 'What is 73 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','26','30'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [915, 916, 917, 918, 919]
},
{
    id: 918,
    question: 'What is 73 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['25','26','27','24'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [916, 917, 918, 919, 920]
},
{
    id: 919,
    question: 'What is 73 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['24','26','27','29'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [917, 918, 919, 920, 921]
},
{
    id: 920,
    question: 'What is 73 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['23','28','26','25'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [918, 919, 920, 921, 922]
},
{
    id: 921,
    question: 'What is 73 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['25','24','26','27'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [919, 920, 921, 922, 923]
},
{
    id: 922,
    question: 'What is 73 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['21','22','20','23'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [920, 921, 922, 923, 924]
},
{
    id: 923,
    question: 'What is 73 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['23','22','25','24'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [921, 922, 923, 924, 925]
},
{
    id: 924,
    question: 'What is 73 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['20','19','21','22'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [922, 923, 924, 925, 926]
},
{
    id: 925,
    question: 'What is 73 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['17','18','19','20'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [923, 924, 925, 926, 927]
},
{
    id: 926,
    question: 'What is 73 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['19','17','18','20'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [924, 925, 926, 927, 928]
},
{
    id: 927,
    question: 'What is 73 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['18','21','16','19'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [925, 926, 927, 928, 929]
},
{
    id: 928,
    question: 'What is 73 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['17','15','14','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [926, 927, 928, 929, 930]
},
{
    id: 929,
    question: 'What is 73 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['14','19','16','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [927, 928, 929, 930, 931]
},
{
    id: 930,
    question: 'What is 73 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['17','16','15','18'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [928, 929, 930, 931, 932]
},
{
    id: 931,
    question: 'What is 73 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['15','17','14','13'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [929, 930, 931, 932, 933]
},
{
    id: 932,
    question: 'What is 73 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','13','16'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [930, 931, 932, 933, 934]
},
{
    id: 933,
    question: 'What is 73 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['9','15','11','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [931, 932, 933, 934, 935]
},
{
    id: 934,
    question: 'What is 73 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['11','8','14','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [932, 933, 934, 935, 936]
},
{
    id: 935,
    question: 'What is 73 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['7','10','9','8'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [933, 934, 935, 936, 937]
},
{
    id: 936,
    question: 'What is 73 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['12','8','9','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [934, 935, 936, 937, 938]
},
{
    id: 937,
    question: 'What is 73 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['10','7','8','11'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [935, 936, 937, 938, 939]
},
{
    id: 938,
    question: 'What is 73 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['6','4','5','7'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [936, 937, 938, 939, 940]
},
{
    id: 939,
    question: 'What is 73 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['7','6','8','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [937, 938, 939, 940, 941]
},
{
    id: 940,
    question: 'What is 73 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['2','5','6','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [938, 939, 940, 941, 942]
},
{
    id: 941,
    question: 'What is 73 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['4','2','7','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [939, 940, 941, 942, 943]
},
{
    id: 942,
    question: 'What is 73 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [940, 941, 942, 943, 944]
},
{
    id: 943,
    question: 'What is 73 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','2','1'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [941, 942, 943, 944, 945]
},
{
    id: 944,
    question: 'What is 73 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [942, 943, 944, 945, 946]
},
{
    id: 945,
    question: 'What is 73 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [945, 944, 946, 947, 948]
},
{
    id: 946,
    question: 'What is 74 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['72','71','74','76'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [944, 945, 946, 947, 948]
},
{
    id: 947,
    question: 'What is 74 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['73','76','75','74'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [945, 946, 947, 948, 949]
},
{
    id: 948,
    question: 'What is 74 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['72','69','71','70'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [946, 947, 948, 949, 950]
},
{
    id: 949,
    question: 'What is 74 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['71','72','69','68'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [947, 948, 949, 950, 951]
},
{
    id: 950,
    question: 'What is 74 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['72','70','73','69'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [948, 949, 950, 951, 952]
},
{
    id: 951,
    question: 'What is 74 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['69','72','70','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [949, 950, 951, 952, 953]
},
{
    id: 952,
    question: 'What is 74 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['69','70','68','65'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [950, 951, 952, 953, 954]
},
{
    id: 953,
    question: 'What is 74 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['67','66','64','70'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [951, 952, 953, 954, 955]
},
{
    id: 954,
    question: 'What is 74 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['64','63','66','67'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [952, 953, 954, 955, 956]
},
{
    id: 955,
    question: 'What is 74 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['64','66','67','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [955, 956, 954, 953, 952]
},
{
    id: 956,
    question: 'What is 74 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['62','63','67','64'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [954, 955, 956, 957, 958]
},
{
    id: 957,
    question: 'What is 74 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['66','62','64','63'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [955, 956, 957, 958, 959]
},
{
    id: 958,
    question: 'What is 74 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['65','63','64','62'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [956, 957, 958, 959, 960]
},
{
    id: 959,
    question: 'What is 74 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['63','60','62','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [957, 958, 959, 960, 961]
},
{
    id: 960,
    question: 'What is 74 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['58','60','59','63'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [958, 959, 960, 961, 962]
},
{
    id: 961,
    question: 'What is 74 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['59','61','60','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [959, 960, 961, 962, 963]
},
{
    id: 962,
    question: 'What is 74 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['58','57','55','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [960, 961, 962, 963, 964]
},
{
    id: 963,
    question: 'What is 74 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['54','55','57','60'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [961, 962, 963, 964, 965]
},
{
    id: 964,
    question: 'What is 74 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['53','59','56','58'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [962, 963, 964, 965, 966]
},
{
    id: 965,
    question: 'What is 74 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['57','58','55','52'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [963, 964, 965, 966, 967]
},
{
    id: 966,
    question: 'What is 74 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['57','54','53','51'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [964, 965, 966, 967, 968]
},
{
    id: 967,
    question: 'What is 74 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['53','51','52','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [965, 966, 967, 968, 969]
},
{
    id: 968,
    question: 'What is 74 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['54','52','55','50'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [966, 967, 968, 969, 970]
},
{
    id: 969,
    question: 'What is 74 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['52','54','51','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [967, 968, 969, 970, 971]
},
{
    id: 970,
    question: 'What is 74 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['48','49','52','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [968, 969, 970, 971, 972]
},
{
    id: 971,
    question: 'What is 74 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','48','46'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [969, 970, 971, 972, 973]
},
{
    id: 972,
    question: 'What is 74 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['49','47','46','48'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [970, 971, 972, 973, 974]
},
{
    id: 973,
    question: 'What is 74 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['46','47','49','48'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [971, 972, 973, 974, 975]
},
{
    id: 974,
    question: 'What is 74 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['45','44','46','43'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [972, 973, 974, 975, 976]
},
{
    id: 975,
    question: 'What is 74 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['45','47','46','43'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [973, 974, 975, 976, 977]
},
{
    id: 976,
    question: 'What is 74 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['46','44','41','43'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [974, 975, 976, 977, 978]
},
{
    id: 977,
    question: 'What is 74 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['43','42','41','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [975, 976, 977, 978, 979]
},
{
    id: 978,
    question: 'What is 74 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['43','45','44','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [976, 977, 978, 979, 980]
},
{
    id: 979,
    question: 'What is 74 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['44','42','41','43'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [977, 978, 979, 980, 981]
},
{
    id: 980,
    question: 'What is 74 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['37','40','39','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [978, 979, 980, 981, 982]
},
{
    id: 981,
    question: 'What is 74 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['42','37','39','38'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [979, 980, 981, 982, 983]
},
{
    id: 982,
    question: 'What is 74 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['37','35','36','38'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [980, 981, 982, 983, 984]
},
{
    id: 983,
    question: 'What is 74 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['38','40','37','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [981, 982, 983, 984, 985]
},
{
    id: 984,
    question: 'What is 74 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['36','34','37','39'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [982, 983, 984, 985, 986]
},
{
    id: 985,
    question: 'What is 74 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['35','34','36','38'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [983, 984, 985, 986, 987]
},
{
    id: 986,
    question: 'What is 74 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['36','34','37','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [984, 985, 986, 987, 988]
},
{
    id: 987,
    question: 'What is 74 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['33','31','36','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [985, 986, 987, 988, 989]
},
{
    id: 988,
    question: 'What is 74 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','30','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [986, 987, 988, 989, 990]
},
{
    id: 989,
    question: 'What is 74 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['32','34','30','31'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [987, 988, 989, 990, 991]
},
{
    id: 990,
    question: 'What is 74 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['29','31','30','27'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [988, 989, 990, 991, 992]
},
{
    id: 991,
    question: 'What is 74 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['32','30','31','29'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [989, 990, 991, 992, 993]
},
{
    id: 992,
    question: 'What is 74 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['31','27','30','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [990, 991, 992, 993, 994]
},
{
    id: 993,
    question: 'What is 74 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','24','27'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [991, 992, 993, 994, 995]
},
{
    id: 994,
    question: 'What is 74 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['24','26','25','29'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [992, 993, 994, 995, 996]
},
{
    id: 995,
    question: 'What is 74 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['23','27','25','26'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [993, 994, 995, 996, 997]
},
{
    id: 996,
    question: 'What is 74 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','26','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [994, 995, 996, 997, 998]
},
{
    id: 997,
    question: 'What is 74 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['23','20','21','24'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [995, 996, 997, 998, 999]
},
{
    id: 998,
    question: 'What is 74 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['24','19','23','22'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [996, 997, 998, 999, 1000]
},
{
    id: 999,
    question: 'What is 74 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['24','23','22','21'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [997, 998, 999, 1000, 1001]
},
{
    id: 1000,
    question: 'What is 74 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['18','20','17','19'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [998, 999, 1000, 1001, 1002]
},
{
    id: 1001,
    question: 'What is 74 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['21','16','22','19'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [999, 1000, 1001, 1002, 1003]
},
{
    id: 1002,
    question: 'What is 74 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['21','20','18','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1000, 1001, 1002, 1003, 1004]
},
{
    id: 1003,
    question: 'What is 74 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['19','17','18','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1001, 1002, 1003, 1004, 1005]
},
{
    id: 1004,
    question: 'What is 74 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['14','16','18','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1002, 1003, 1004, 1005, 1006]
},
{
    id: 1005,
    question: 'What is 74 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['16','14','13','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1003, 1004, 1005, 1006, 1007]
},
{
    id: 1006,
    question: 'What is 74 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['13','14','12','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1004, 1005, 1006, 1007, 1008]
},
{
    id: 1007,
    question: 'What is 74 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['13','12','15','11'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1005, 1006, 1007, 1008, 1009]
},
{
    id: 1008,
    question: 'What is 74 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['12','14','15','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1006, 1007, 1008, 1009, 1010]
},
{
    id: 1009,
    question: 'What is 74 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','9','8'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1007, 1008, 1009, 1010, 1011]
},
{
    id: 1010,
    question: 'What is 74 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['10','13','12','7'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1008, 1009, 1010, 1011, 1012]
},
{
    id: 1011,
    question: 'What is 74 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['6','12','9','7'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1009, 1010, 1011, 1012, 1013]
},
{
    id: 1012,
    question: 'What is 74 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['7','5','9','8'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1010, 1011, 1012, 1013, 1014]
},
{
    id: 1013,
    question: 'What is 74 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['10','9','6','7'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1011, 1012, 1013, 1014, 1015]
},
{
    id: 1014,
    question: 'What is 74 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['4','6','7','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1012, 1013, 1014, 1015, 1016]
},
{
    id: 1015,
    question: 'What is 74 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['4','5','7','6'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1013, 1014, 1015, 1016, 1017]
},
{
    id: 1016,
    question: 'What is 74 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['1','5','4','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1014, 1015, 1016, 1017, 1018]
},
{
    id: 1017,
    question: 'What is 74 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1015, 1016, 1017, 1018, 1019]
},
{
    id: 1018,
    question: 'What is 74 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','3','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1016, 1017, 1018, 1019, 1020]
},
{
    id: 1019,
    question: 'What is 74 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1017, 1018, 1019, 1020, 1021]
},
{
    id: 1020,
    question: 'What is 74 - 74 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1020, 1019, 1021, 1022, 1023]
},
{
    id: 1021,
    question: 'What is 75 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['75','78','73','72'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1019, 1020, 1021, 1022, 1023]
},
{
    id: 1022,
    question: 'What is 75 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['71','73','76','74'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1020, 1021, 1022, 1023, 1024]
},
{
    id: 1023,
    question: 'What is 75 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['72','70','71','73'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1021, 1022, 1023, 1024, 1025]
},
{
    id: 1024,
    question: 'What is 75 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['69','71','72','75'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1022, 1023, 1024, 1025, 1026]
},
{
    id: 1025,
    question: 'What is 75 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['74','71','68','70'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1023, 1024, 1025, 1026, 1027]
},
{
    id: 1026,
    question: 'What is 75 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['73','71','72','70'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1024, 1025, 1026, 1027, 1028]
},
{
    id: 1027,
    question: 'What is 75 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['71','69','67','66'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1025, 1026, 1027, 1028, 1029]
},
{
    id: 1028,
    question: 'What is 75 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['71','67','68','70'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1026, 1027, 1028, 1029, 1030]
},
{
    id: 1029,
    question: 'What is 75 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['67','64','66','68'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1027, 1028, 1029, 1030, 1031]
},
{
    id: 1030,
    question: 'What is 75 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['63','66','69','65'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1030, 1031, 1029, 1028, 1027]
},
{
    id: 1031,
    question: 'What is 75 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['63','62','66','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1029, 1030, 1031, 1032, 1033]
},
{
    id: 1032,
    question: 'What is 75 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['67','64','65','61'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1030, 1031, 1032, 1033, 1034]
},
{
    id: 1033,
    question: 'What is 75 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['61','64','63','65'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1031, 1032, 1033, 1034, 1035]
},
{
    id: 1034,
    question: 'What is 75 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['62','64','65','63'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1032, 1033, 1034, 1035, 1036]
},
{
    id: 1035,
    question: 'What is 75 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['59','60','61','63'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1033, 1034, 1035, 1036, 1037]
},
{
    id: 1036,
    question: 'What is 75 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['58','60','62','63'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1034, 1035, 1036, 1037, 1038]
},
{
    id: 1037,
    question: 'What is 75 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['62','61','60','59'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1035, 1036, 1037, 1038, 1039]
},
{
    id: 1038,
    question: 'What is 75 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['57','59','60','58'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1036, 1037, 1038, 1039, 1040]
},
{
    id: 1039,
    question: 'What is 75 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['58','59','56','57'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1037, 1038, 1039, 1040, 1041]
},
{
    id: 1040,
    question: 'What is 75 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['53','58','56','59'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1038, 1039, 1040, 1041, 1042]
},
{
    id: 1041,
    question: 'What is 75 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['53','52','55','54'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1039, 1040, 1041, 1042, 1043]
},
{
    id: 1042,
    question: 'What is 75 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['55','57','56','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1040, 1041, 1042, 1043, 1044]
},
{
    id: 1043,
    question: 'What is 75 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['56','55','53','51'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1041, 1042, 1043, 1044, 1045]
},
{
    id: 1044,
    question: 'What is 75 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['54','52','55','53'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1042, 1043, 1044, 1045, 1046]
},
{
    id: 1045,
    question: 'What is 75 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['50','48','49','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1043, 1044, 1045, 1046, 1047]
},
{
    id: 1046,
    question: 'What is 75 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['50','53','52','49'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1044, 1045, 1046, 1047, 1048]
},
{
    id: 1047,
    question: 'What is 75 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['49','50','47','46'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1045, 1046, 1047, 1048, 1049]
},
{
    id: 1048,
    question: 'What is 75 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['46','49','48','45'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1046, 1047, 1048, 1049, 1050]
},
{
    id: 1049,
    question: 'What is 75 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['50','44','49','47'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1047, 1048, 1049, 1050, 1051]
},
{
    id: 1050,
    question: 'What is 75 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['48','47','46','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1048, 1049, 1050, 1051, 1052]
},
{
    id: 1051,
    question: 'What is 75 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['47','44','42','45'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1049, 1050, 1051, 1052, 1053]
},
{
    id: 1052,
    question: 'What is 75 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['46','44','41','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1050, 1051, 1052, 1053, 1054]
},
{
    id: 1053,
    question: 'What is 75 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['45','43','46','44'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1051, 1052, 1053, 1054, 1055]
},
{
    id: 1054,
    question: 'What is 75 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['41','42','40','39'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1052, 1053, 1054, 1055, 1056]
},
{
    id: 1055,
    question: 'What is 75 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['40','39','38','41'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1053, 1054, 1055, 1056, 1057]
},
{
    id: 1056,
    question: 'What is 75 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['43','37','40','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1054, 1055, 1056, 1057, 1058]
},
{
    id: 1057,
    question: 'What is 75 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['37','39','36','38'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1055, 1056, 1057, 1058, 1059]
},
{
    id: 1058,
    question: 'What is 75 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['37','40','38','36'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1056, 1057, 1058, 1059, 1060]
},
{
    id: 1059,
    question: 'What is 75 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['34','40','38','37'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1057, 1058, 1059, 1060, 1061]
},
{
    id: 1060,
    question: 'What is 75 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['36','39','38','37'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1058, 1059, 1060, 1061, 1062]
},
{
    id: 1061,
    question: 'What is 75 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['34','36','37','35'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1059, 1060, 1061, 1062, 1063]
},
{
    id: 1062,
    question: 'What is 75 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['34','32','31','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1060, 1061, 1062, 1063, 1064]
},
{
    id: 1063,
    question: 'What is 75 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['35','30','32','33'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1061, 1062, 1063, 1064, 1065]
},
{
    id: 1064,
    question: 'What is 75 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','29','30'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1062, 1063, 1064, 1065, 1066]
},
{
    id: 1065,
    question: 'What is 75 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['30','31','32','28'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1063, 1064, 1065, 1066, 1067]
},
{
    id: 1066,
    question: 'What is 75 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['30','31','32','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1064, 1065, 1066, 1067, 1068]
},
{
    id: 1067,
    question: 'What is 75 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['29','30','31','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1065, 1066, 1067, 1068, 1069]
},
{
    id: 1068,
    question: 'What is 75 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','27','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1066, 1067, 1068, 1069, 1070]
},
{
    id: 1069,
    question: 'What is 75 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['28','24','27','25'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1067, 1068, 1069, 1070, 1071]
},
{
    id: 1070,
    question: 'What is 75 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['23','26','29','27'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1068, 1069, 1070, 1071, 1072]
},
{
    id: 1071,
    question: 'What is 75 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['22','27','25','26'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1069, 1070, 1071, 1072, 1073]
},
{
    id: 1072,
    question: 'What is 75 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['26','27','22','24'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1070, 1071, 1072, 1073, 1074]
},
{
    id: 1073,
    question: 'What is 75 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['24','23','20','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1071, 1072, 1073, 1074, 1075]
},
{
    id: 1074,
    question: 'What is 75 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['24','22','19','20'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1072, 1073, 1074, 1075, 1076]
},
{
    id: 1075,
    question: 'What is 75 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['21','23','24','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1073, 1074, 1075, 1076, 1077]
},
{
    id: 1076,
    question: 'What is 75 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['20','18','22','19'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1074, 1075, 1076, 1077, 1078]
},
{
    id: 1077,
    question: 'What is 75 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['19','16','21','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1075, 1076, 1077, 1078, 1079]
},
{
    id: 1078,
    question: 'What is 75 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['19','16','21','18'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1076, 1077, 1078, 1079, 1080]
},
{
    id: 1079,
    question: 'What is 75 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['15','17','18','20'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1077, 1078, 1079, 1080, 1081]
},
{
    id: 1080,
    question: 'What is 75 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['16','13','17','14'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1078, 1079, 1080, 1081, 1082]
},
{
    id: 1081,
    question: 'What is 75 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['14','13','16','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1079, 1080, 1081, 1082, 1083]
},
{
    id: 1082,
    question: 'What is 75 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['14','12','13','15'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1080, 1081, 1082, 1083, 1084]
},
{
    id: 1083,
    question: 'What is 75 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['14','10','12','13'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1081, 1082, 1083, 1084, 1085]
},
{
    id: 1084,
    question: 'What is 75 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['12','10','14','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1082, 1083, 1084, 1085, 1086]
},
{
    id: 1085,
    question: 'What is 75 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['13','12','11','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1083, 1084, 1085, 1086, 1087]
},
{
    id: 1086,
    question: 'What is 75 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['7','10','13','8'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1084, 1085, 1086, 1087, 1088]
},
{
    id: 1087,
    question: 'What is 75 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['9','7','11','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1085, 1086, 1087, 1088, 1089]
},
{
    id: 1088,
    question: 'What is 75 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['8','9','5','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1086, 1087, 1088, 1089, 1090]
},
{
    id: 1089,
    question: 'What is 75 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['4','5','7','6'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1087, 1088, 1089, 1090, 1091]
},
{
    id: 1090,
    question: 'What is 75 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['3','6','4','9'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1088, 1089, 1090, 1091, 1092]
},
{
    id: 1091,
    question: 'What is 75 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['2','8','6','5'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1089, 1090, 1091, 1092, 1093]
},
{
    id: 1092,
    question: 'What is 75 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['5','1','4','7'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1090, 1091, 1092, 1093, 1094]
},
{
    id: 1093,
    question: 'What is 75 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','3','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1091, 1092, 1093, 1094, 1095]
},
{
    id: 1094,
    question: 'What is 75 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1092, 1093, 1094, 1095, 1096]
},
{
    id: 1095,
    question: 'What is 75 - 74 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1093, 1094, 1095, 1096, 1097]
},
{
    id: 1096,
    question: 'What is 75 - 75 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','2','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1096, 1095, 1097, 1098, 1099]
},
{
    id: 1097,
    question: 'What is 76 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['76','77','74','75'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1095, 1096, 1097, 1098, 1099]
},
{
    id: 1098,
    question: 'What is 76 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['76','74','75','78'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1096, 1097, 1098, 1099, 1100]
},
{
    id: 1099,
    question: 'What is 76 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['75','74','73','77'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1097, 1098, 1099, 1100, 1101]
},
{
    id: 1100,
    question: 'What is 76 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['73','74','76','72'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1098, 1099, 1100, 1101, 1102]
},
{
    id: 1101,
    question: 'What is 76 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['70','72','69','74'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1099, 1100, 1101, 1102, 1103]
},
{
    id: 1102,
    question: 'What is 76 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['71','74','73','72'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1100, 1101, 1102, 1103, 1104]
},
{
    id: 1103,
    question: 'What is 76 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['73','70','71','72'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1101, 1102, 1103, 1104, 1105]
},
{
    id: 1104,
    question: 'What is 76 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['68','67','69','66'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1102, 1103, 1104, 1105, 1106]
},
{
    id: 1105,
    question: 'What is 76 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['65','68','66','71'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1103, 1104, 1105, 1106, 1107]
},
{
    id: 1106,
    question: 'What is 76 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['66','67','70','68'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1106, 1107, 1105, 1104, 1103]
},
{
    id: 1107,
    question: 'What is 76 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['68','67','66','64'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1105, 1106, 1107, 1108, 1109]
},
{
    id: 1108,
    question: 'What is 76 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['62','63','64','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1106, 1107, 1108, 1109, 1110]
},
{
    id: 1109,
    question: 'What is 76 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['67','61','66','64'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1107, 1108, 1109, 1110, 1111]
},
{
    id: 1110,
    question: 'What is 76 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['61','63','62','66'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1108, 1109, 1110, 1111, 1112]
},
{
    id: 1111,
    question: 'What is 76 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['64','63','62','65'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1109, 1110, 1111, 1112, 1113]
},
{
    id: 1112,
    question: 'What is 76 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['64','60','58','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1110, 1111, 1112, 1113, 1114]
},
{
    id: 1113,
    question: 'What is 76 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['57','58','60','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1111, 1112, 1113, 1114, 1115]
},
{
    id: 1114,
    question: 'What is 76 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['60','61','59','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1112, 1113, 1114, 1115, 1116]
},
{
    id: 1115,
    question: 'What is 76 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['61','59','58','57'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1113, 1114, 1115, 1116, 1117]
},
{
    id: 1116,
    question: 'What is 76 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['56','57','58','60'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1114, 1115, 1116, 1117, 1118]
},
{
    id: 1117,
    question: 'What is 76 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['53','59','57','56'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1115, 1116, 1117, 1118, 1119]
},
{
    id: 1118,
    question: 'What is 76 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['53','56','55','57'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1116, 1117, 1118, 1119, 1120]
},
{
    id: 1119,
    question: 'What is 76 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['56','52','51','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1117, 1118, 1119, 1120, 1121]
},
{
    id: 1120,
    question: 'What is 76 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['52','53','51','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1118, 1119, 1120, 1121, 1122]
},
{
    id: 1121,
    question: 'What is 76 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['52','54','49','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1119, 1120, 1121, 1122, 1123]
},
{
    id: 1122,
    question: 'What is 76 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['51','52','53','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1120, 1121, 1122, 1123, 1124]
},
{
    id: 1123,
    question: 'What is 76 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['52','53','51','50'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1121, 1122, 1123, 1124, 1125]
},
{
    id: 1124,
    question: 'What is 76 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['50','46','49','52'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1122, 1123, 1124, 1125, 1126]
},
{
    id: 1125,
    question: 'What is 76 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['48','45','46','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1123, 1124, 1125, 1126, 1127]
},
{
    id: 1126,
    question: 'What is 76 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['47','45','46','44'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1124, 1125, 1126, 1127, 1128]
},
{
    id: 1127,
    question: 'What is 76 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['49','48','46','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1125, 1126, 1127, 1128, 1129]
},
{
    id: 1128,
    question: 'What is 76 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['42','43','45','44'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1126, 1127, 1128, 1129, 1130]
},
{
    id: 1129,
    question: 'What is 76 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['47','42','43','44'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1127, 1128, 1129, 1130, 1131]
},
{
    id: 1130,
    question: 'What is 76 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['46','42','40','43'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1128, 1129, 1130, 1131, 1132]
},
{
    id: 1131,
    question: 'What is 76 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['45','42','40','41'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1129, 1130, 1131, 1132, 1133]
},
{
    id: 1132,
    question: 'What is 76 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['39','44','42','41'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1130, 1131, 1132, 1133, 1134]
},
{
    id: 1133,
    question: 'What is 76 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['40','38','41','42'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1131, 1132, 1133, 1134, 1135]
},
{
    id: 1134,
    question: 'What is 76 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['40','39','38','36'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1132, 1133, 1134, 1135, 1136]
},
{
    id: 1135,
    question: 'What is 76 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['38','36','39','35'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1133, 1134, 1135, 1136, 1137]
},
{
    id: 1136,
    question: 'What is 76 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['39','36','34','37'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1134, 1135, 1136, 1137, 1138]
},
{
    id: 1137,
    question: 'What is 76 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['37','34','36','38'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1135, 1136, 1137, 1138, 1139]
},
{
    id: 1138,
    question: 'What is 76 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['35','38','32','36'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1136, 1137, 1138, 1139, 1140]
},
{
    id: 1139,
    question: 'What is 76 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['33','35','31','34'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1137, 1138, 1139, 1140, 1141]
},
{
    id: 1140,
    question: 'What is 76 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['31','30','33','35'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1138, 1139, 1140, 1141, 1142]
},
{
    id: 1141,
    question: 'What is 76 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['35','34','33','32'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1139, 1140, 1141, 1142, 1143]
},
{
    id: 1142,
    question: 'What is 76 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['32','34','33','31'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1140, 1141, 1142, 1143, 1144]
},
{
    id: 1143,
    question: 'What is 76 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['31','32','33','30'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1141, 1142, 1143, 1144, 1145]
},
{
    id: 1144,
    question: 'What is 76 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['32','29','28','27'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1142, 1143, 1144, 1145, 1146]
},
{
    id: 1145,
    question: 'What is 76 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['28','26','27','31'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1143, 1144, 1145, 1146, 1147]
},
{
    id: 1146,
    question: 'What is 76 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['28','24','27','26'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1144, 1145, 1146, 1147, 1148]
},
{
    id: 1147,
    question: 'What is 76 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['29','26','27','28'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1145, 1146, 1147, 1148, 1149]
},
{
    id: 1148,
    question: 'What is 76 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['25','23','28','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1146, 1147, 1148, 1149, 1150]
},
{
    id: 1149,
    question: 'What is 76 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['21','27','22','24'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1147, 1148, 1149, 1150, 1151]
},
{
    id: 1150,
    question: 'What is 76 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['24','21','23','26'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1148, 1149, 1150, 1151, 1152]
},
{
    id: 1151,
    question: 'What is 76 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['22','19','23','25'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1149, 1150, 1151, 1152, 1153]
},
{
    id: 1152,
    question: 'What is 76 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['23','22','20','21'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1150, 1151, 1152, 1153, 1154]
},
{
    id: 1153,
    question: 'What is 76 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['21','17','20','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1151, 1152, 1153, 1154, 1155]
},
{
    id: 1154,
    question: 'What is 76 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['22','19','18','20'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1152, 1153, 1154, 1155, 1156]
},
{
    id: 1155,
    question: 'What is 76 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['21','20','17','18'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1153, 1154, 1155, 1156, 1157]
},
{
    id: 1156,
    question: 'What is 76 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['16','17','15','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1154, 1155, 1156, 1157, 1158]
},
{
    id: 1157,
    question: 'What is 76 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['16','17','14','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1155, 1156, 1157, 1158, 1159]
},
{
    id: 1158,
    question: 'What is 76 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['16','15','18','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1156, 1157, 1158, 1159, 1160]
},
{
    id: 1159,
    question: 'What is 76 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['12','14','15','17'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1157, 1158, 1159, 1160, 1161]
},
{
    id: 1160,
    question: 'What is 76 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['11','10','13','16'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1158, 1159, 1160, 1161, 1162]
},
{
    id: 1161,
    question: 'What is 76 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['11','14','15','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1159, 1160, 1161, 1162, 1163]
},
{
    id: 1162,
    question: 'What is 76 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['8','11','9','10'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1160, 1161, 1162, 1163, 1164]
},
{
    id: 1163,
    question: 'What is 76 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['13','10','11','9'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1161, 1162, 1163, 1164, 1165]
},
{
    id: 1164,
    question: 'What is 76 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['8','6','9','12'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1162, 1163, 1164, 1165, 1166]
},
{
    id: 1165,
    question: 'What is 76 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['8','11','6','10'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1163, 1164, 1165, 1166, 1167]
},
{
    id: 1166,
    question: 'What is 76 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['9','7','10','6'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1164, 1165, 1166, 1167, 1168]
},
{
    id: 1167,
    question: 'What is 76 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['3','5','6','4'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1165, 1166, 1167, 1168, 1169]
},
{
    id: 1168,
    question: 'What is 76 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['5','2','7','4'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1166, 1167, 1168, 1169, 1170]
},
{
    id: 1169,
    question: 'What is 76 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['4','3','2','1'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1167, 1168, 1169, 1170, 1171]
},
{
    id: 1170,
    question: 'What is 76 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1168, 1169, 1170, 1171, 1172]
},
{
    id: 1171,
    question: 'What is 76 - 74 ?',
    answers: ['2','3','0','1'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1169, 1170, 1171, 1172, 1173]
},
{
    id: 1172,
    question: 'What is 76 - 75 ?',
    answers: ['0','1','2','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1170, 1171, 1172, 1173, 1174]
},
{
    id: 1173,
    question: 'What is 76 - 76 ?',
    answers: ['2','0','1','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1173, 1172, 1174, 1175, 1176]
},
{
    id: 1174,
    question: 'What is 77 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['80','75','79','77'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1172, 1173, 1174, 1175, 1176]
},
{
    id: 1175,
    question: 'What is 77 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['76','77','73','75'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1173, 1174, 1175, 1176, 1177]
},
{
    id: 1176,
    question: 'What is 77 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['75','74','72','73'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1174, 1175, 1176, 1177, 1178]
},
{
    id: 1177,
    question: 'What is 77 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['71','74','75','72'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1175, 1176, 1177, 1178, 1179]
},
{
    id: 1178,
    question: 'What is 77 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['73','74','76','75'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1176, 1177, 1178, 1179, 1180]
},
{
    id: 1179,
    question: 'What is 77 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['74','72','71','73'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1177, 1178, 1179, 1180, 1181]
},
{
    id: 1180,
    question: 'What is 77 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['69','71','73','72'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1178, 1179, 1180, 1181, 1182]
},
{
    id: 1181,
    question: 'What is 77 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['70','67','69','72'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1179, 1180, 1181, 1182, 1183]
},
{
    id: 1182,
    question: 'What is 77 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['69','67','66','68'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1180, 1181, 1182, 1183, 1184]
},
{
    id: 1183,
    question: 'What is 77 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['69','71','68','70'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1183, 1184, 1182, 1181, 1180]
},
{
    id: 1184,
    question: 'What is 77 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['66','67','64','69'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1182, 1183, 1184, 1185, 1186]
},
{
    id: 1185,
    question: 'What is 77 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['63','69','65','66'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1183, 1184, 1185, 1186, 1187]
},
{
    id: 1186,
    question: 'What is 77 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['64','65','68','66'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1184, 1185, 1186, 1187, 1188]
},
{
    id: 1187,
    question: 'What is 77 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['67','65','64','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1185, 1186, 1187, 1188, 1189]
},
{
    id: 1188,
    question: 'What is 77 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['61','63','62','60'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1186, 1187, 1188, 1189, 1190]
},
{
    id: 1189,
    question: 'What is 77 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['62','61','59','63'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1187, 1188, 1189, 1190, 1191]
},
{
    id: 1190,
    question: 'What is 77 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['61','59','62','60'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1188, 1189, 1190, 1191, 1192]
},
{
    id: 1191,
    question: 'What is 77 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['60','57','61','63'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1189, 1190, 1191, 1192, 1193]
},
{
    id: 1192,
    question: 'What is 77 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['58','57','59','62'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1190, 1191, 1192, 1193, 1194]
},
{
    id: 1193,
    question: 'What is 77 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['59','58','60','56'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1191, 1192, 1193, 1194, 1195]
},
{
    id: 1194,
    question: 'What is 77 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['57','60','56','55'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1192, 1193, 1194, 1195, 1196]
},
{
    id: 1195,
    question: 'What is 77 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['54','56','53','59'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1193, 1194, 1195, 1196, 1197]
},
{
    id: 1196,
    question: 'What is 77 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['52','56','57','55'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1194, 1195, 1196, 1197, 1198]
},
{
    id: 1197,
    question: 'What is 77 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['52','56','54','53'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1195, 1196, 1197, 1198, 1199]
},
{
    id: 1198,
    question: 'What is 77 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['53','50','52','51'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1196, 1197, 1198, 1199, 1200]
},
{
    id: 1199,
    question: 'What is 77 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['50','52','49','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1197, 1198, 1199, 1200, 1201]
},
{
    id: 1200,
    question: 'What is 77 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['48','54','53','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1198, 1199, 1200, 1201, 1202]
},
{
    id: 1201,
    question: 'What is 77 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['50','51','52','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1199, 1200, 1201, 1202, 1203]
},
{
    id: 1202,
    question: 'What is 77 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['52','49','48','51'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1200, 1201, 1202, 1203, 1204]
},
{
    id: 1203,
    question: 'What is 77 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['48','50','47','46'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1201, 1202, 1203, 1204, 1205]
},
{
    id: 1204,
    question: 'What is 77 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['44','45','47','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1202, 1203, 1204, 1205, 1206]
},
{
    id: 1205,
    question: 'What is 77 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['46','48','44','45'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1203, 1204, 1205, 1206, 1207]
},
{
    id: 1206,
    question: 'What is 77 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['47','45','44','48'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1204, 1205, 1206, 1207, 1208]
},
{
    id: 1207,
    question: 'What is 77 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['44','46','43','41'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1205, 1206, 1207, 1208, 1209]
},
{
    id: 1208,
    question: 'What is 77 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['41','40','43','45'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1206, 1207, 1208, 1209, 1210]
},
{
    id: 1209,
    question: 'What is 77 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['42','45','43','41'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1207, 1208, 1209, 1210, 1211]
},
{
    id: 1210,
    question: 'What is 77 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['42','43','41','39'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1208, 1209, 1210, 1211, 1212]
},
{
    id: 1211,
    question: 'What is 77 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['43','40','37','42'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1209, 1210, 1211, 1212, 1213]
},
{
    id: 1212,
    question: 'What is 77 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['41','39','36','38'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1210, 1211, 1212, 1213, 1214]
},
{
    id: 1213,
    question: 'What is 77 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['39','38','35','40'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1211, 1212, 1213, 1214, 1215]
},
{
    id: 1214,
    question: 'What is 77 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['37','39','34','36'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1212, 1213, 1214, 1215, 1216]
},
{
    id: 1215,
    question: 'What is 77 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['39','37','36','38'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1213, 1214, 1215, 1216, 1217]
},
{
    id: 1216,
    question: 'What is 77 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['32','35','34','33'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1214, 1215, 1216, 1217, 1218]
},
{
    id: 1217,
    question: 'What is 77 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['37','32','34','33'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1215, 1216, 1217, 1218, 1219]
},
{
    id: 1218,
    question: 'What is 77 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['30','31','33','35'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1216, 1217, 1218, 1219, 1220]
},
{
    id: 1219,
    question: 'What is 77 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','30','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1217, 1218, 1219, 1220, 1221]
},
{
    id: 1220,
    question: 'What is 77 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['29','34','32','31'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1218, 1219, 1220, 1221, 1222]
},
{
    id: 1221,
    question: 'What is 77 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['29','33','30','31'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1219, 1220, 1221, 1222, 1223]
},
{
    id: 1222,
    question: 'What is 77 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['29','30','31','32'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1220, 1221, 1222, 1223, 1224]
},
{
    id: 1223,
    question: 'What is 77 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['25','26','30','28'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1221, 1222, 1223, 1224, 1225]
},
{
    id: 1224,
    question: 'What is 77 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['27','24','29','30'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1222, 1223, 1224, 1225, 1226]
},
{
    id: 1225,
    question: 'What is 77 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['25','29','26','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1223, 1224, 1225, 1226, 1227]
},
{
    id: 1226,
    question: 'What is 77 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['22','23','24','25'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1224, 1225, 1226, 1227, 1228]
},
{
    id: 1227,
    question: 'What is 77 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['21','24','26','22'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1225, 1226, 1227, 1228, 1229]
},
{
    id: 1228,
    question: 'What is 77 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['26','24','23','22'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1226, 1227, 1228, 1229, 1230]
},
{
    id: 1229,
    question: 'What is 77 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['21','25','19','22'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1227, 1228, 1229, 1230, 1231]
},
{
    id: 1230,
    question: 'What is 77 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['18','21','24','22'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1228, 1229, 1230, 1231, 1232]
},
{
    id: 1231,
    question: 'What is 77 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['17','20','18','22'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1229, 1230, 1231, 1232, 1233]
},
{
    id: 1232,
    question: 'What is 77 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['18','20','21','19'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1230, 1231, 1232, 1233, 1234]
},
{
    id: 1233,
    question: 'What is 77 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['18','19','21','20'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1231, 1232, 1233, 1234, 1235]
},
{
    id: 1234,
    question: 'What is 77 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['20','17','16','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1232, 1233, 1234, 1235, 1236]
},
{
    id: 1235,
    question: 'What is 77 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['17','14','15','16'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1233, 1234, 1235, 1236, 1237]
},
{
    id: 1236,
    question: 'What is 77 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['17','12','15','14'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1234, 1235, 1236, 1237, 1238]
},
{
    id: 1237,
    question: 'What is 77 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['15','14','16','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1235, 1236, 1237, 1238, 1239]
},
{
    id: 1238,
    question: 'What is 77 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['10','13','12','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1236, 1237, 1238, 1239, 1240]
},
{
    id: 1239,
    question: 'What is 77 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['13','15','9','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1237, 1238, 1239, 1240, 1241]
},
{
    id: 1240,
    question: 'What is 77 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['9','11','10','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1238, 1239, 1240, 1241, 1242]
},
{
    id: 1241,
    question: 'What is 77 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['13','11','10','7'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1239, 1240, 1241, 1242, 1243]
},
{
    id: 1242,
    question: 'What is 77 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['9','6','10','7'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1240, 1241, 1242, 1243, 1244]
},
{
    id: 1243,
    question: 'What is 77 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['7','8','5','6'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1241, 1242, 1243, 1244, 1245]
},
{
    id: 1244,
    question: 'What is 77 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['7','8','10','9'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1242, 1243, 1244, 1245, 1246]
},
{
    id: 1245,
    question: 'What is 77 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['6','9','4','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1243, 1244, 1245, 1246, 1247]
},
{
    id: 1246,
    question: 'What is 77 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','7','5'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1244, 1245, 1246, 1247, 1248]
},
{
    id: 1247,
    question: 'What is 77 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['4','5','7','3'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1245, 1246, 1247, 1248, 1249]
},
{
    id: 1248,
    question: 'What is 77 - 74 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','0','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1246, 1247, 1248, 1249, 1250]
},
{
    id: 1249,
    question: 'What is 77 - 75 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','0','1'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1247, 1248, 1249, 1250, 1251]
},
{
    id: 1250,
    question: 'What is 77 - 76 ?',
    answers: ['0','2','3','1'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1248, 1249, 1250, 1251, 1252]
},
{
    id: 1251,
    question: 'What is 77 - 77 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','2','0'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1251, 1250, 1252, 1253, 1254]
},
{
    id: 1252,
    question: 'What is 78 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['78','80','81','79'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1250, 1251, 1252, 1253, 1254]
},
{
    id: 1253,
    question: 'What is 78 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['76','74','77','75'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1251, 1252, 1253, 1254, 1255]
},
{
    id: 1254,
    question: 'What is 78 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['79','75','73','76'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1252, 1253, 1254, 1255, 1256]
},
{
    id: 1255,
    question: 'What is 78 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['75','72','74','73'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1253, 1254, 1255, 1256, 1257]
},
{
    id: 1256,
    question: 'What is 78 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['71','77','74','72'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1254, 1255, 1256, 1257, 1258]
},
{
    id: 1257,
    question: 'What is 78 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['72','71','73','70'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1255, 1256, 1257, 1258, 1259]
},
{
    id: 1258,
    question: 'What is 78 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['72','75','71','74'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1256, 1257, 1258, 1259, 1260]
},
{
    id: 1259,
    question: 'What is 78 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['71','72','70','73'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1257, 1258, 1259, 1260, 1261]
},
{
    id: 1260,
    question: 'What is 78 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['67','70','68','72'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1258, 1259, 1260, 1261, 1262]
},
{
    id: 1261,
    question: 'What is 78 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['68','72','69','66'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1261, 1262, 1260, 1259, 1258]
},
{
    id: 1262,
    question: 'What is 78 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['68','70','69','67'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1260, 1261, 1262, 1263, 1264]
},
{
    id: 1263,
    question: 'What is 78 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['69','66','67','68'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1261, 1262, 1263, 1264, 1265]
},
{
    id: 1264,
    question: 'What is 78 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['66','65','64','63'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1262, 1263, 1264, 1265, 1266]
},
{
    id: 1265,
    question: 'What is 78 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['65','63','62','67'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1263, 1264, 1265, 1266, 1267]
},
{
    id: 1266,
    question: 'What is 78 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['64','62','63','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1264, 1265, 1266, 1267, 1268]
},
{
    id: 1267,
    question: 'What is 78 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['65','62','66','63'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1265, 1266, 1267, 1268, 1269]
},
{
    id: 1268,
    question: 'What is 78 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['60','62','61','59'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1266, 1267, 1268, 1269, 1270]
},
{
    id: 1269,
    question: 'What is 78 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['61','59','58','62'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1267, 1268, 1269, 1270, 1271]
},
{
    id: 1270,
    question: 'What is 78 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['60','59','62','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1268, 1269, 1270, 1271, 1272]
},
{
    id: 1271,
    question: 'What is 78 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['56','58','57','59'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1269, 1270, 1271, 1272, 1273]
},
{
    id: 1272,
    question: 'What is 78 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['55','61','60','58'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1270, 1271, 1272, 1273, 1274]
},
{
    id: 1273,
    question: 'What is 78 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['57','58','54','55'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1271, 1272, 1273, 1274, 1275]
},
{
    id: 1274,
    question: 'What is 78 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['55','57','54','56'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1272, 1273, 1274, 1275, 1276]
},
{
    id: 1275,
    question: 'What is 78 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['52','55','53','54'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1273, 1274, 1275, 1276, 1277]
},
{
    id: 1276,
    question: 'What is 78 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['55','53','56','54'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1274, 1275, 1276, 1277, 1278]
},
{
    id: 1277,
    question: 'What is 78 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['56','51','54','53'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1275, 1276, 1277, 1278, 1279]
},
{
    id: 1278,
    question: 'What is 78 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['52','53','49','54'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1276, 1277, 1278, 1279, 1280]
},
{
    id: 1279,
    question: 'What is 78 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['51','52','49','54'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1277, 1278, 1279, 1280, 1281]
},
{
    id: 1280,
    question: 'What is 78 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['50','48','51','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1278, 1279, 1280, 1281, 1282]
},
{
    id: 1281,
    question: 'What is 78 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['49','47','50','48'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1279, 1280, 1281, 1282, 1283]
},
{
    id: 1282,
    question: 'What is 78 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['48','46','49','47'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1280, 1281, 1282, 1283, 1284]
},
{
    id: 1283,
    question: 'What is 78 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['49','48','44','47'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1281, 1282, 1283, 1284, 1285]
},
{
    id: 1284,
    question: 'What is 78 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['49','46','47','43'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1282, 1283, 1284, 1285, 1286]
},
{
    id: 1285,
    question: 'What is 78 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['47','45','48','43'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1283, 1284, 1285, 1286, 1287]
},
{
    id: 1286,
    question: 'What is 78 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['42','44','46','41'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1284, 1285, 1286, 1287, 1288]
},
{
    id: 1287,
    question: 'What is 78 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['44','42','43','46'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1285, 1286, 1287, 1288, 1289]
},
{
    id: 1288,
    question: 'What is 78 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['39','44','42','43'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1286, 1287, 1288, 1289, 1290]
},
{
    id: 1289,
    question: 'What is 78 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['38','41','39','40'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1287, 1288, 1289, 1290, 1291]
},
{
    id: 1290,
    question: 'What is 78 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['39','38','40','37'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1288, 1289, 1290, 1291, 1292]
},
{
    id: 1291,
    question: 'What is 78 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','39','40'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1289, 1290, 1291, 1292, 1293]
},
{
    id: 1292,
    question: 'What is 78 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['39','38','41','37'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1290, 1291, 1292, 1293, 1294]
},
{
    id: 1293,
    question: 'What is 78 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['37','36','35','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1291, 1292, 1293, 1294, 1295]
},
{
    id: 1294,
    question: 'What is 78 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['34','38','37','36'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1292, 1293, 1294, 1295, 1296]
},
{
    id: 1295,
    question: 'What is 78 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['35','38','37','36'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1293, 1294, 1295, 1296, 1297]
},
{
    id: 1296,
    question: 'What is 78 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['34','31','36','33'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1294, 1295, 1296, 1297, 1298]
},
{
    id: 1297,
    question: 'What is 78 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['35','33','32','31'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1295, 1296, 1297, 1298, 1299]
},
{
    id: 1298,
    question: 'What is 78 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['29','32','33','35'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1296, 1297, 1298, 1299, 1300]
},
{
    id: 1299,
    question: 'What is 78 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['34','31','30','33'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1297, 1298, 1299, 1300, 1301]
},
{
    id: 1300,
    question: 'What is 78 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['33','29','30','31'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1298, 1299, 1300, 1301, 1302]
},
{
    id: 1301,
    question: 'What is 78 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['29','32','30','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1299, 1300, 1301, 1302, 1303]
},
{
    id: 1302,
    question: 'What is 78 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','29','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1300, 1301, 1302, 1303, 1304]
},
{
    id: 1303,
    question: 'What is 78 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['27','25','24','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1301, 1302, 1303, 1304, 1305]
},
{
    id: 1304,
    question: 'What is 78 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['28','25','24','26'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1302, 1303, 1304, 1305, 1306]
},
{
    id: 1305,
    question: 'What is 78 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['25','22','23','24'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1303, 1304, 1305, 1306, 1307]
},
{
    id: 1306,
    question: 'What is 78 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['26','24','22','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1304, 1305, 1306, 1307, 1308]
},
{
    id: 1307,
    question: 'What is 78 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['23','25','24','21'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1305, 1306, 1307, 1308, 1309]
},
{
    id: 1308,
    question: 'What is 78 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['23','25','24','22'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1306, 1307, 1308, 1309, 1310]
},
{
    id: 1309,
    question: 'What is 78 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['23','22','21','24'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1307, 1308, 1309, 1310, 1311]
},
{
    id: 1310,
    question: 'What is 78 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['18','19','20','17'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1308, 1309, 1310, 1311, 1312]
},
{
    id: 1311,
    question: 'What is 78 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','16','22'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1309, 1310, 1311, 1312, 1313]
},
{
    id: 1312,
    question: 'What is 78 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','20','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1310, 1311, 1312, 1313, 1314]
},
{
    id: 1313,
    question: 'What is 78 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['15','18','17','20'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1311, 1312, 1313, 1314, 1315]
},
{
    id: 1314,
    question: 'What is 78 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['15','18','13','16'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1312, 1313, 1314, 1315, 1316]
},
{
    id: 1315,
    question: 'What is 78 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['14','16','13','15'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1313, 1314, 1315, 1316, 1317]
},
{
    id: 1316,
    question: 'What is 78 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['14','16','17','13'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1314, 1315, 1316, 1317, 1318]
},
{
    id: 1317,
    question: 'What is 78 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['14','15','11','13'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1315, 1316, 1317, 1318, 1319]
},
{
    id: 1318,
    question: 'What is 78 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['13','12','15','10'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1316, 1317, 1318, 1319, 1320]
},
{
    id: 1319,
    question: 'What is 78 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['12','8','9','11'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1317, 1318, 1319, 1320, 1321]
},
{
    id: 1320,
    question: 'What is 78 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['7','10','9','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1318, 1319, 1320, 1321, 1322]
},
{
    id: 1321,
    question: 'What is 78 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['7','10','12','9'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1319, 1320, 1321, 1322, 1323]
},
{
    id: 1322,
    question: 'What is 78 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['10','8','9','11'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1320, 1321, 1322, 1323, 1324]
},
{
    id: 1323,
    question: 'What is 78 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['7','5','10','6'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1321, 1322, 1323, 1324, 1325]
},
{
    id: 1324,
    question: 'What is 78 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['9','7','5','6'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1322, 1323, 1324, 1325, 1326]
},
{
    id: 1325,
    question: 'What is 78 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['3','5','4','7'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1323, 1324, 1325, 1326, 1327]
},
{
    id: 1326,
    question: 'What is 78 - 74 ?',
    answers: ['6','4','7','5'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1324, 1325, 1326, 1327, 1328]
},
{
    id: 1327,
    question: 'What is 78 - 75 ?',
    answers: ['1','0','2','3'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1325, 1326, 1327, 1328, 1329]
},
{
    id: 1328,
    question: 'What is 78 - 76 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','2','0'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1326, 1327, 1328, 1329, 1330]
},
{
    id: 1329,
    question: 'What is 78 - 77 ?',
    answers: ['1','3','2','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1327, 1328, 1329, 1330, 1331]
},
{
    id: 1330,
    question: 'What is 78 - 78 ?',
    answers: ['3','0','1','2'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1330, 1329, 1331, 1332, 1333]
},
{
    id: 1331,
    question: 'What is 79 - 0 ?',
    answers: ['78','79','76','77'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1329, 1330, 1331, 1332, 1333]
},
{
    id: 1332,
    question: 'What is 79 - 1 ?',
    answers: ['78','81','76','75'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1330, 1331, 1332, 1333, 1334]
},
{
    id: 1333,
    question: 'What is 79 - 2 ?',
    answers: ['74','77','78','79'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1331, 1332, 1333, 1334, 1335]
},
{
    id: 1334,
    question: 'What is 79 - 3 ?',
    answers: ['79','78','75','76'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1332, 1333, 1334, 1335, 1336]
},
{
    id: 1335,
    question: 'What is 79 - 4 ?',
    answers: ['78','76','75','77'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1333, 1334, 1335, 1336, 1337]
},
{
    id: 1336,
    question: 'What is 79 - 5 ?',
    answers: ['71','73','74','76'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1334, 1335, 1336, 1337, 1338]
},
{
    id: 1337,
    question: 'What is 79 - 6 ?',
    answers: ['75','71','70','73'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1335, 1336, 1337, 1338, 1339]
},
{
    id: 1338,
    question: 'What is 79 - 7 ?',
    answers: ['69','74','73','72'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1336, 1337, 1338, 1339, 1340]
},
{
    id: 1339,
    question: 'What is 79 - 8 ?',
    answers: ['71','68','72','70'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1337, 1338, 1339, 1340, 1341]
},
{
    id: 1340,
    question: 'What is 79 - 9 ?',
    answers: ['68','70','69','67'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1340, 1341, 1339, 1338, 1337]
},
{
    id: 1341,
    question: 'What is 79 - 10 ?',
    answers: ['68','71','69','72'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1339, 1340, 1341, 1342, 1343]
},
{
    id: 1342,
    question: 'What is 79 - 11 ?',
    answers: ['68','65','71','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1340, 1341, 1342, 1343, 1344]
},
{
    id: 1343,
    question: 'What is 79 - 12 ?',
    answers: ['67','68','65','70'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1341, 1342, 1343, 1344, 1345]
},
{
    id: 1344,
    question: 'What is 79 - 13 ?',
    answers: ['64','68','66','63'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1342, 1343, 1344, 1345, 1346]
},
{
    id: 1345,
    question: 'What is 79 - 14 ?',
    answers: ['68','67','62','65'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1343, 1344, 1345, 1346, 1347]
},
{
    id: 1346,
    question: 'What is 79 - 15 ?',
    answers: ['64','65','67','66'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1344, 1345, 1346, 1347, 1348]
},
{
    id: 1347,
    question: 'What is 79 - 16 ?',
    answers: ['63','61','66','64'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1345, 1346, 1347, 1348, 1349]
},
{
    id: 1348,
    question: 'What is 79 - 17 ?',
    answers: ['62','60','59','61'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1346, 1347, 1348, 1349, 1350]
},
{
    id: 1349,
    question: 'What is 79 - 18 ?',
    answers: ['60','59','62','61'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1347, 1348, 1349, 1350, 1351]
},
{
    id: 1350,
    question: 'What is 79 - 19 ?',
    answers: ['57','58','62','60'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1348, 1349, 1350, 1351, 1352]
},
{
    id: 1351,
    question: 'What is 79 - 20 ?',
    answers: ['62','59','58','56'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1349, 1350, 1351, 1352, 1353]
},
{
    id: 1352,
    question: 'What is 79 - 21 ?',
    answers: ['60','61','55','58'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1350, 1351, 1352, 1353, 1354]
},
{
    id: 1353,
    question: 'What is 79 - 22 ?',
    answers: ['55','56','58','57'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1351, 1352, 1353, 1354, 1355]
},
{
    id: 1354,
    question: 'What is 79 - 23 ?',
    answers: ['56','59','58','57'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1352, 1353, 1354, 1355, 1356]
},
{
    id: 1355,
    question: 'What is 79 - 24 ?',
    answers: ['54','58','52','55'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1353, 1354, 1355, 1356, 1357]
},
{
    id: 1356,
    question: 'What is 79 - 25 ?',
    answers: ['54','56','55','51'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1354, 1355, 1356, 1357, 1358]
},
{
    id: 1357,
    question: 'What is 79 - 26 ?',
    answers: ['53','51','50','56'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1355, 1356, 1357, 1358, 1359]
},
{
    id: 1358,
    question: 'What is 79 - 27 ?',
    answers: ['52','50','51','53'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1356, 1357, 1358, 1359, 1360]
},
{
    id: 1359,
    question: 'What is 79 - 28 ?',
    answers: ['52','50','49','51'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1357, 1358, 1359, 1360, 1361]
},
{
    id: 1360,
    question: 'What is 79 - 29 ?',
    answers: ['48','50','47','49'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1358, 1359, 1360, 1361, 1362]
},
{
    id: 1361,
    question: 'What is 79 - 30 ?',
    answers: ['52','49','48','46'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1359, 1360, 1361, 1362, 1363]
},
{
    id: 1362,
    question: 'What is 79 - 31 ?',
    answers: ['45','51','48','47'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1360, 1361, 1362, 1363, 1364]
},
{
    id: 1363,
    question: 'What is 79 - 32 ?',
    answers: ['48','50','47','49'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1361, 1362, 1363, 1364, 1365]
},
{
    id: 1364,
    question: 'What is 79 - 33 ?',
    answers: ['47','49','48','46'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1362, 1363, 1364, 1365, 1366]
},
{
    id: 1365,
    question: 'What is 79 - 34 ?',
    answers: ['43','44','45','42'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1363, 1364, 1365, 1366, 1367]
},
{
    id: 1366,
    question: 'What is 79 - 35 ?',
    answers: ['46','47','45','44'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1364, 1365, 1366, 1367, 1368]
},
{
    id: 1367,
    question: 'What is 79 - 36 ?',
    answers: ['45','46','44','43'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1365, 1366, 1367, 1368, 1369]
},
{
    id: 1368,
    question: 'What is 79 - 37 ?',
    answers: ['41','45','43','42'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1366, 1367, 1368, 1369, 1370]
},
{
    id: 1369,
    question: 'What is 79 - 38 ?',
    answers: ['41','40','38','39'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1367, 1368, 1369, 1370, 1371]
},
{
    id: 1370,
    question: 'What is 79 - 39 ?',
    answers: ['40','37','43','38'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1368, 1369, 1370, 1371, 1372]
},
{
    id: 1371,
    question: 'What is 79 - 40 ?',
    answers: ['40','42','39','41'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1369, 1370, 1371, 1372, 1373]
},
{
    id: 1372,
    question: 'What is 79 - 41 ?',
    answers: ['38','37','41','40'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1370, 1371, 1372, 1373, 1374]
},
{
    id: 1373,
    question: 'What is 79 - 42 ?',
    answers: ['36','40','35','37'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1371, 1372, 1373, 1374, 1375]
},
{
    id: 1374,
    question: 'What is 79 - 43 ?',
    answers: ['34','35','36','33'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1372, 1373, 1374, 1375, 1376]
},
{
    id: 1375,
    question: 'What is 79 - 44 ?',
    answers: ['36','37','34','35'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1373, 1374, 1375, 1376, 1377]
},
{
    id: 1376,
    question: 'What is 79 - 45 ?',
    answers: ['35','37','34','32'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1374, 1375, 1376, 1377, 1378]
},
{
    id: 1377,
    question: 'What is 79 - 46 ?',
    answers: ['33','30','32','34'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1375, 1376, 1377, 1378, 1379]
},
{
    id: 1378,
    question: 'What is 79 - 47 ?',
    answers: ['30','34','32','29'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1376, 1377, 1378, 1379, 1380]
},
{
    id: 1379,
    question: 'What is 79 - 48 ?',
    answers: ['32','31','34','33'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1377, 1378, 1379, 1380, 1381]
},
{
    id: 1380,
    question: 'What is 79 - 49 ?',
    answers: ['32','30','33','27'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1378, 1379, 1380, 1381, 1382]
},
{
    id: 1381,
    question: 'What is 79 - 50 ?',
    answers: ['29','27','26','30'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1379, 1380, 1381, 1382, 1383]
},
{
    id: 1382,
    question: 'What is 79 - 51 ?',
    answers: ['28','30','26','27'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1380, 1381, 1382, 1383, 1384]
},
{
    id: 1383,
    question: 'What is 79 - 52 ?',
    answers: ['25','27','28','26'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1381, 1382, 1383, 1384, 1385]
},
{
    id: 1384,
    question: 'What is 79 - 53 ?',
    answers: ['24','26','25','23'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1382, 1383, 1384, 1385, 1386]
},
{
    id: 1385,
    question: 'What is 79 - 54 ?',
    answers: ['25','23','24','26'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1383, 1384, 1385, 1386, 1387]
},
{
    id: 1386,
    question: 'What is 79 - 55 ?',
    answers: ['22','24','26','25'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1384, 1385, 1386, 1387, 1388]
},
{
    id: 1387,
    question: 'What is 79 - 56 ?',
    answers: ['25','23','22','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1385, 1386, 1387, 1388, 1389]
},
{
    id: 1388,
    question: 'What is 79 - 57 ?',
    answers: ['25','24','22','23'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1386, 1387, 1388, 1389, 1390]
},
{
    id: 1389,
    question: 'What is 79 - 58 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','23','21'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1387, 1388, 1389, 1390, 1391]
},
{
    id: 1390,
    question: 'What is 79 - 59 ?',
    answers: ['18','17','21','20'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1388, 1389, 1390, 1391, 1392]
},
{
    id: 1391,
    question: 'What is 79 - 60 ?',
    answers: ['19','22','16','18'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1389, 1390, 1391, 1392, 1393]
},
{
    id: 1392,
    question: 'What is 79 - 61 ?',
    answers: ['19','18','17','21'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1390, 1391, 1392, 1393, 1394]
},
{
    id: 1393,
    question: 'What is 79 - 62 ?',
    answers: ['16','14','15','17'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1391, 1392, 1393, 1394, 1395]
},
{
    id: 1394,
    question: 'What is 79 - 63 ?',
    answers: ['18','16','14','15'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1392, 1393, 1394, 1395, 1396]
},
{
    id: 1395,
    question: 'What is 79 - 64 ?',
    answers: ['16','15','17','14'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1393, 1394, 1395, 1396, 1397]
},
{
    id: 1396,
    question: 'What is 79 - 65 ?',
    answers: ['14','17','15','16'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1394, 1395, 1396, 1397, 1398]
},
{
    id: 1397,
    question: 'What is 79 - 66 ?',
    answers: ['13','15','11','14'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1395, 1396, 1397, 1398, 1399]
},
{
    id: 1398,
    question: 'What is 79 - 67 ?',
    answers: ['15','13','9','12'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1396, 1397, 1398, 1399, 1400]
},
{
    id: 1399,
    question: 'What is 79 - 68 ?',
    answers: ['10','14','11','9'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1397, 1398, 1399, 1400, 1401]
},
{
    id: 1400,
    question: 'What is 79 - 69 ?',
    answers: ['13','12','8','10'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1398, 1399, 1400, 1401, 1402]
},
{
    id: 1401,
    question: 'What is 79 - 70 ?',
    answers: ['7','9','10','12'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1399, 1400, 1401, 1402, 1403]
},
{
    id: 1402,
    question: 'What is 79 - 71 ?',
    answers: ['9','11','8','10'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1400, 1401, 1402, 1403, 1404]
},
{
    id: 1403,
    question: 'What is 79 - 72 ?',
    answers: ['9','8','10','7'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1401, 1402, 1403, 1404, 1405]
},
{
    id: 1404,
    question: 'What is 79 - 73 ?',
    answers: ['4','9','7','6'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1402, 1403, 1404, 1405, 1406]
},
{
    id: 1405,
    question: 'What is 79 - 74 ?',
    answers: ['2','5','4','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1403, 1404, 1405, 1406, 1407]
},
{
    id: 1406,
    question: 'What is 79 - 75 ?',
    answers: ['6','4','2','3'],
    correct: 2,
    similar: [1404, 1405, 1406, 1407, 1408]
},
{
    id: 1407,
    question: 'What is 79 - 76 ?',
    answers: ['3','2','1','0'],
    correct: 1,
    similar: [1405, 1406, 1407, 1408, 1409]
},
{
    id: 1408,
    question: 'What is 79 - 77 ?',
    answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1406, 1407, 1408, 1409, 1410]
},
{
    id: 1409,
    question: 'What is 79 - 78 ?',
    answers: ['2','0','3','1'],
    correct: 4,
    similar: [1407, 1408, 1409, 1410, 1411]
},
{
    id: 1410,
    question: 'What is 79 - 79 ?',
    answers: ['3','1','0','2'],
    correct: 3,
    similar: [1410, 1409, 1411, 1412, 1413]
},
]
